<tutor>
    <setspec>
        <lessonname>Survey for A&amp;P Students</lessonname>
        <userselect>true</userselect>
        <stimulusfile>IESsurveystims.xml</stimulusfile>
        <lfparameter>.85</lfparameter>

        <shuffleclusters>30-159</shuffleclusters>
    </setspec>
    <unit>
        <unitname>Informed Consent</unitname>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[
          <center><table width="738" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" border="2">
  	<tbody>
  		<tr>
  			<td colspan="2" width="738">
  				<center>
  				<h3>	<strong>Consent for Research Participation</strong></h3>
        </center>
  			</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td width="380">
  				<p>
  					<strong>Title</strong>
  				</p>
  				<p>
  					<strong> </strong>
  				</p>
  			</td>
  			<td width="358" valign="top">
  				<p>
  					Using Adaptive Practice to Improve Recall and Understanding
  					in Postsecondary Anatomy and Physiology
  				</p>
  			</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td width="380">
  				<p>
  					<strong>Sponsor</strong>
  				</p>
  			</td>
  			<td width="358" valign="top">
  				<p>
  					Department of Education, Institute of Educational Science
  				</p>
  			</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td width="380">
  				<p>
  					<strong>Researcher(s)</strong>
  				</p>
  			</td>
  			<td width="358" valign="top">
  				<p>
  					Philip Pavlik, University of Memphis
  				</p>
  				<p>
  					Andrew Olney, University of Memphis
  				</p>
  				<p>
  					Amanda Banker, Southwest Tennessee Community College
  				</p>
  			</td>
  		</tr>
  		<tr>
  			<td width="380">
  				<p>
  					<strong>Researchers Contact Information</strong>
  				</p>
  			</td>
  			<td width="358">
  				<p>
  					412-605-0581, ppavlik@memphis.edu
  				</p>
  			</td>
  		</tr>
  	</tbody>
  </table></center>
          <p>
            You are being asked to participate in a research study. The box below
            highlights key information for you to consider when deciding if you want to
            participate. More detailed information is provided below the box. Please
            ask the researcher(s) any questions about the study before you make your
            decision. If you volunteer, you will be one of about 150 people to do so.
          </p>
          <center><table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" border="2">
            <tbody>
              <tr>
                <td width="714" valign="top">
                  <p align="center">
                    <strong>Key Information for You to Consider</strong>
                  </p>
                </td>
              </tr>
              <tr>
                <td width="714" valign="top">
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Voluntary Consent: </u></strong>
                    You are being asked to volunteer for a research study. It
                    is up to you whether you choose to participate or not.
                    There will be no penalty or loss of benefit to which you
                    are otherwise entitled if you choose not to participate or
                    discontinue participation.
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Purpose:</u></strong>
                    The purpose of the study is to help us understand results
                    from an adaptive practice system for Anatomy and
                    Physiology. You are being invited to participate because
                    are a student in a participating section of Anatomy and
                    Physiology at Southwest Tennessee Community College.
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Duration:</u></strong>
                    It is expected that your participation will last 30 minutes
                    or less.
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Procedures and Activities</u></strong>
                    : You will be asked some demographic questions to get a
                    better idea of past experience of students. There will also
                    be a survey of author recognition to get an idea how much
                    reading you do in your spare time.
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Risk:</u></strong>
                    Some of the foreseeable risk or discomforts of your
                    participation include boredom or stress if you find the
                    author recognition difficult.
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Benefits:</u></strong>
                    The benefit is in helping us improve the system for future
                    students. This may improve student learning and success.
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <strong><u>Alternatives</u></strong>
                    : Participation is voluntary, and the only alternative is
                    to not participate. As a student if you decide not to take
                    part in this study your choice will have no effect on your
                    academic status or grade in your class.
                  </p>
                </td>
              </tr>
            </tbody>
          </table></center>
          <p>
            <h3>Who is conducting this research?</h3>
          </p>
          <p>
            Philip Pavlik of the University of Memphis, Institute of Intelligent
            Systems and Department of Psychology is in charge of the study. There may
            be other research team members assisting during the study.
          </p>
            <h3>What happens if I agree to participate in this Research?</h3>

          <p>
            If you agree you will be asked to answer 30 quick demographics questions
            and then try to identify authors from a list of 65 authors that will be
            presented.
          </p>
            <h3>
              What happens to the information collected for this research?
            </h3>
          <p>
            By participating, you understand and agree that the deidentified data
            gathered during this study may be used by the University of Memphis and
            published and/or disclosed by the University of Memphis to others outside
            of the University of Memphis. However, no personally identifying
            information will ever be mentioned in any such publication or dissemination
            of the research data and/or results to other researchers. In fact, we will
            never receive any personally identifying information in the course of this
            study.
          </p>
          <p>
            <h3>How will my privacy and data confidentiality be protected?</h3>
          </p>
          <p>
            We are very careful to protect student's identity in the course of this
            research. Our data collection strategy is designed to never expose the true
            identity of students to our research team. Data-linkage will occur through
            a random login ID distributed to each student the first week of the course.
            Your instructors have been carefully informed that they should not share
            the identities of students with us, so we will only identify you with your
            assigned login. Only teachers will create the keys to match logins to
            individuals. We do not log GPS or IP address information. We will further
            deidentify your data (remove your ID) after the experiment before storing
            it on our computers long-term..
          </p>

            <h3>What if I want to stop participating in this research?</h3>

          <p>
            It is up to you to decide whether you want to volunteer for this study. It
            is also ok to decide to end your participation at any time. There is no
            penalty or loss of benefits to which you are otherwise entitled if you
            decided to withdraw your participation. Your decision about participating
            will not affect your relationship with the researcher(s) or the University
          of Memphis or Southwest Tennessee Community College.
          </p>
          <h3>
            Will it cost me money to take part in this research?
          </h3>
          <p>
            No.
          </p>
          <h3>
            Will I receive any compensation or reward for participating in this
            research?
          </h3>
          <p>
            Your professor will distribute a $10 Macy's gift card if you complete this
            survey before the chapter 11 exam. Professors will distribute
            the gift cards to the students who completed the survey.
          </p>
          <h3>
            Who can answer my question about this research?
          </h3>
          <p>
        Before you decide to volunteer for this study, if you have questions, suggestions, concerns, or complaints about the
            study, you can contact the investigator, Dr. Philip Pavlik at 412-605-0581
          or email	<a href="mailto:ppavlik@memphis.edu">ppavlik@memphis.edu</a>. If you
            have any questions about your rights as a volunteer in this research,
            contact the Institutional Review Board staff at the University of Memphis
          at 901-678-2705 or email	<a href="mailto:irb@memphis.edu">irb@memphis.edu</a>. You may print this
            screen webpage for your records.
          </p>
          <p>
            <center><strong>STATEMENT OF CONSENT </strong></center>
          </p>
          <p>
            I have had the opportunity to consider the information in this form. I have
            asked any questions needed for me to decide about my participation. I
            understand that I can ask additional questions though the study.
          </p>
          <p>
            By clicking below, I am electronically signing, I volunteer to participate
            in this research. I understand that I am not waiving any legal rights. I
            may print a copy of this form.
          </p>




          ]]> </unitinstructions>
    </unit>
    <unit>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[This is the survey to get the 10$ gift certificate. There are 2 parts, first with 30 questions and second with 65 questions. Be sure you have logged in with the special ID
        your instructor gave you. These random ID allow us to match data to grades without knowing who you are.]]></unitinstructions>
        <unitname>Survey for A&amp;P Students</unitname>
          <buttonorder>fixed</buttonorder>
        <assessmentsession>
            <conditiontemplatesbygroup>
                <groupnames>A</groupnames>
                <clustersrepeated>1</clustersrepeated>
                <templatesrepeated>30</templatesrepeated>
                <group>0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
                0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
              0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0</group>
            </conditiontemplatesbygroup>
            <initialpositions> A_1 A_2 A_3 A_4 A_5 A_6 A_7 A_8 A_9 A_10
A_11 A_12 A_13 A_14 A_15 A_16 A_17 A_18 A_19 A_20
A_21 A_22 A_23 A_24 A_25 A_26 A_27 A_28 A_29 A_30
            </initialpositions>
            <randomizegroups>false</randomizegroups>
            <clusterlist>0-29</clusterlist>
            <assignrandomclusters>false</assignrandomclusters>
            <permutefinalresult>0-0</permutefinalresult>
        </assessmentsession>
        <deliveryparams>
            <drill>10000000</drill>
            <purestudy>16000</purestudy>
            <skipstudy>false</skipstudy>
            <reviewstudy>0</reviewstudy>
            <correctprompt>0</correctprompt>
            <fontsize>2</fontsize>
            <correctscore>0</correctscore>
            <incorrectscore>0</incorrectscore>
        </deliveryparams>
    </unit>
    <unit>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[The following survey tests your recall of authors. Please pick TRUE if you are sure it is a real author and pick FALSE if you are not sure or know it is fake.]]></unitinstructions>
        <unitname>Author Recognition Survey for A&amp;P Students</unitname>
          <buttonorder>fixed</buttonorder>
          <wrongButtonOptions>True, False</wrongButtonOptions>
        <assessmentsession>
            <conditiontemplatesbygroup>
                <groupnames>A</groupnames>
                <clustersrepeated>1</clustersrepeated>
                <templatesrepeated>65</templatesrepeated>
                <group>0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
                  0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
                  0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
              0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
              0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
            0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0
            0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 0,b,t,0 </group>
            </conditiontemplatesbygroup>
            <initialpositions> A_1	A_2	A_3	A_4	A_5	A_6	A_7	A_8	A_9	A_10
              A_11	A_12	A_13	A_14	A_15	A_16	A_17	A_18	A_19	A_20
              A_21	A_22	A_23	A_24	A_25	A_26	A_27	A_28	A_29	A_30
              A_31	A_32	A_33	A_34	A_35	A_36	A_37	A_38	A_39	A_40
              A_41	A_42	A_43	A_44	A_45	A_46	A_47	A_48	A_49	A_50
              A_51	A_52	A_53	A_54	A_55	A_56	A_57	A_58	A_59	A_60
              A_61	A_62	A_63	A_64	A_65
            </initialpositions>
            <randomizegroups>false</randomizegroups>
            <clusterlist>30-94</clusterlist>
            <assignrandomclusters>false</assignrandomclusters>
            <permutefinalresult>0-0</permutefinalresult>
        </assessmentsession>
        <deliveryparams>
            <drill>10000000</drill>
            <purestudy>16000</purestudy>
            <skipstudy>false</skipstudy>
            <reviewstudy>0</reviewstudy>
            <correctprompt>0</correctprompt>
            <fontsize>2</fontsize>
            <correctscore>0</correctscore>
            <incorrectscore>0</incorrectscore>
        </deliveryparams>
    </unit>
    <unit>
        <unitname>last</unitname>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[Thanks for the information, we hope it will help us to understand the results of our research. Your instructor will tell you when the gift cards are available, (after chapter 12 exam is completed).]]></unitinstructions>
    </unit>
</tutor>
