<tutor>
    <setspec>
       
        <name>Intro Practice</name>
        <lessonname>Intro Instructive</lessonname>
        <userselect>false</userselect>
        <experimentTarget>introins</experimentTarget>
        <stimulusfile>IntroCorrectivestims.json</stimulusfile>
    </setspec>  
    <unit>
        <unitname>Informed Consent</unitname>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[<p>The experiment is designed to compare various degrees of corrective feedback while studying for an upcoming exam. You have been randomly assigned to this condition. Whatever condition you are in, please try to do your best, as this is a useful study tool. 
<p>If you should have any questions about this research study please feel free to contact your course instructor, or Kaitlyn Peperone at kpperone@memphis.edu. For questions regarding the research subjects' rights, the Chair of the Institutional Review Board for the Protection of Human Subjects should be contacted at 901-678-2705.
<p>All efforts, within the limits allowed by law, will be made to keep the personal information in your research record private but total privacy cannot be promised. We will deidentify your data after the experiment before storing it on our computers long-term. By participating, you understand and agree that the deidentified data gathered during this study may be used by University of Memphis and published and/or disclosed by University of Memphis to others outside of University of Memphis. However, no personally identifying information will ever be mentioned in any such publication or dissemination of the research data and/or results to other researchers.
<br><br><p align="center">By clicking this continue button, I consent to the above terms.]]> </unitinstructions>

    </unit>
   
    <unit>
        <unitname>Text Instuctions</unitname>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[<p>The terms and facts you are about to see are representative of those you will tested on for the exam. You must review the terms and facts for a minimum of 15 minutes to receive extra credit. You may return to the review after the 15 minutes is up. You may find it useful to take notes on the topics throughout the 15 minutes. <br><br> If you have any questions about the system, please contact your course instructor. <br><br> Please remember to email your course instructor the 4 digit sequence that you used to log into the system.</p>]]></unitinstructions>
    </unit>
    <unit>
        <unitname>Text</unitname>
        <instructionminseconds>900</instructionminseconds>
        <instructionmaxseconds>900</instructionmaxseconds>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[Operational definitions are an exact set of procedures used to represent a particular concept.
<br><br>
Gestalt psychologists studied thinking, learning, and perception in whole units, as opposed to analyzing these experiences in smaller units.
<br><br>
Sigmund Freud, the founder of psychoanalytic psychology, believed that our unconscious thoughts, impulses, and desires strongly influenced our behaviors.
<br><br>
Psychiatrists are medical doctors who treat psychological disorders with medication.
<br><br>
Experiments require a researchers to create two groups (a control group and an experimental group), vary a condition among the groups, and record data of the effects in each condition.
<br><br>
Dependent variables measure results of an experiment and are directly affected by the independent variables. Dependent variable are often revealed by measures of performance.
<br><br>
Random assignment of participants to each condition within an experiment can be used to minimize effects of extraneous variables that might unintentionally affect the outcome of the experiment.
<br><br>
The control group and the experimental group in an experiment are treated exactly the same except for the independent variable.
<br><br>
Placebos are often given to participants within the control group to make them believe they have been given the drug, or the true independent variable. 
<br><br>
In a single-blind study, participants are unaware of who is in the experimental group and who is in the control group, but the experimenters do know the members of each group.
<br><br>
A double-blind experiment is one in which neither the participants, nor the experimenters, are aware of who is in the experimental group and who is in the control group.
<br><br>
The observer effect states that participants may change their behaviors when they are aware that they are being watched. 
<br><br>
A negative correlation is one in which a decrease in one measure is matched with an increase in another measure. The measures will always move in the opposite direction of each other.
<br><br>
A positive correlation is one in which a decrease or increase in one measure is matched with a movement in the same direction in the other measure. The measures will always move in the same direction as each other.
<br><br>
Events that occur immediately before the response are called antecedents.
<br><br>
Linking a neutral antecedent stimulus with a stimulus that does produces an involuntary response is called classical conditioning.
<br><br>
Classical conditioning is based on the antecedents, or what happens before a behavior or response. An antecedent is called a stimulus when it is used during classical conditioning. 
<br><br>
Shaping is the gradual molding of responses to a desired pattern of behavior(s).
<br><br>
Negative reinforcements increase the probability of repeating a response.
<br><br>
Punishments are events that follow responses and decrease the likelihood of that response occurring again.
<br><br>
Token economies use secondary, token, reinforcers to provide positive reinforcement after a behavior. These tokens can then later be exchanged for primary reinforcers.
<br><br>
Variable ratio schedules of reinforcement present a reinforcement after an unpredictable amount of time and are the most resistant to extinction.
<br><br>
Out of the three tools used to control behavior (nonreinforcement, reinforcement, and punishment), it is usually best to use positive reinforcement.
<br><br>
The three basic processes of memory are encoding, storage, and retrieval.
<br><br>
Encoding is the process of memory in which sensory information is converted into a form that can be stored in memory.
<br><br>
Storage is the process of memory in which encoded information is held for later use.
<br><br>
Chunking involves grouping bits of information into larger units as a way to improve the efficiency of short-term memory.
<br><br>
Elaborative processing involves linking new information to previously encoded and stored knowledge and memories, and is the most effective way to transfer short-term memories into long-term storage. 
<br><br>
Spreading activation refers to reconstructing memories by starting with one recollection and following chains of associations to other related memories.
<br><br>
The serial position effect says that you are most likely to forget the middle items on a list while remembering the first and last items on that list.
<br><br>
Sequential lineups are ones in which a witness is shown one photo at a time.
<br><br>
State dependent learning refers to the fact that bodily states and moods can be encoded and stored as part of a memory, and therefore be a strong cue for later recall of that memory.
<br><br>
Sleeping after studying can increase memory because there is less interference during sleep.
<br><br>
Interference is the tendency for new memories to get in the way of recalling old memories, or for old memories to get in the way of recalling new memories.
<br><br>
Consolidation is the formation of long-term memories in the brain. ]]>


</unitinstructions>
    </unit>
      <unit>
        <unitname>Continuation</unitname>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[<p>You have completed the extra credit. Please continue practicing if you want. <br><br> Please remember to email your course instructor the 4 digit sequence that you used to log into the system.</p>]]></unitinstructions>
    </unit>
    <unit>
        <unitname>Text-2</unitname>
        <instructionminseconds>1000000</instructionminseconds>
        <instructionmaxseconds>1000000</instructionmaxseconds>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[Operational definitions are an exact set of procedures used to represent a particular concept.
<br><br>
Gestalt psychologists studied thinking, learning, and perception in whole units, as opposed to analyzing these experiences in smaller units.
<br><br>
Sigmund Freud, the founder of psychoanalytic psychology, believed that our unconscious thoughts, impulses, and desires strongly influenced our behaviors.
<br><br>
Psychiatrists are medical doctors who treat psychological disorders with medication.
<br><br>
Experiments require a researchers to create two groups (a control group and an experimental group), vary a condition among the groups, and record data of the effects in each condition.
<br><br>
Dependent variables measure results of an experiment and are directly affected by the independent variables. Dependent variable are often revealed by measures of performance.
<br><br>
Random assignment of participants to each condition within an experiment can be used to minimize effects of extraneous variables that might unintentionally affect the outcome of the experiment.
<br><br>
The control group and the experimental group in an experiment are treated exactly the same except for the independent variable.
<br><br>
Placebos are often given to participants within the control group to make them believe they have been given the drug, or the true independent variable. 
<br><br>
In a single-blind study, participants are unaware of who is in the experimental group and who is in the control group, but the experimenters do know the members of each group.
<br><br>
A double-blind experiment is one in which neither the participants, nor the experimenters, are aware of who is in the experimental group and who is in the control group.
<br><br>
The observer effect states that participants may change their behaviors when they are aware that they are being watched. 
<br><br>
A negative correlation is one in which a decrease in one measure is matched with an increase in another measure. The measures will always move in the opposite direction of each other.
<br><br>
A positive correlation is one in which a decrease or increase in one measure is matched with a movement in the same direction in the other measure. The measures will always move in the same direction as each other.
<br><br>
Events that occur immediately before the response are called antecedents.
<br><br>
Linking a neutral antecedent stimulus with a stimulus that does produces an involuntary response is called classical conditioning.
<br><br>
Classical conditioning is based on the antecedents, or what happens before a behavior or response. An antecedent is called a stimulus when it is used during classical conditioning. 
<br><br>
Shaping is the gradual molding of responses to a desired pattern of behavior(s).
<br><br>
Negative reinforcements increase the probability of repeating a response.
<br><br>
Punishments are events that follow responses and decrease the likelihood of that response occurring again.
<br><br>
Token economies use secondary, token, reinforcers to provide positive reinforcement after a behavior. These tokens can then later be exchanged for primary reinforcers.
<br><br>
Variable ratio schedules of reinforcement present a reinforcement after an unpredictable amount of time and are the most resistant to extinction.
<br><br>
Out of the three tools used to control behavior (nonreinforcement, reinforcement, and punishment), it is usually best to use positive reinforcement.
<br><br>
The three basic processes of memory are encoding, storage, and retrieval.
<br><br>
Encoding is the process of memory in which sensory information is converted into a form that can be stored in memory.
<br><br>
Storage is the process of memory in which encoded information is held for later use.
<br><br>
Chunking involves grouping bits of information into larger units as a way to improve the efficiency of short-term memory.
<br><br>
Elaborative processing involves linking new information to previously encoded and stored knowledge and memories, and is the most effective way to transfer short-term memories into long-term storage. 
<br><br>
Spreading activation refers to reconstructing memories by starting with one recollection and following chains of associations to other related memories.
<br><br>
The serial position effect says that you are most likely to forget the middle items on a list while remembering the first and last items on that list.
<br><br>
Sequential lineups are ones in which a witness is shown one photo at a time.
<br><br>
State dependent learning refers to the fact that bodily states and moods can be encoded and stored as part of a memory, and therefore be a strong cue for later recall of that memory.
<br><br>
Sleeping after studying can increase memory because there is less interference during sleep.
<br><br>
Interference is the tendency for new memories to get in the way of recalling old memories, or for old memories to get in the way of recalling new memories.
<br><br>
Consolidation is the formation of long-term memories in the brain. ]]>


</unitinstructions>
    </unit>
    <unit>
       
        <unitname>last</unitname>
        <unitinstructions><![CDATA[You have now completed the practice. ]]></unitinstructions>
    </unit>
</tutor>
