<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<setspec>
  <clusters>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the time it took to do that, a decision made in a part of your brain that controls skeletal muscles resulted in impulses along motor neuron axons to the muscles in your hand, releasing acetylcholine at __________.</display>
      <response>neuromuscular junctions</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the time it took to do that, a decision made in a part of your brain that controls skeletal muscles resulted in impulses along __________ to the muscles in your hand, releasing acetylcholine at neuromuscular junctions.</display>
      <response>motor neuron axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the time it took to do that, a decision made in a part of your brain that controls skeletal muscles resulted in impulses along motor neuron axons to the muscles in your hand, releasing __________ at neuromuscular junctions.</display>
      <response>acetylcholine</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An __________ is a cylindrical process that conducts impulses away from a neuron cell body.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An axon is a cylindrical process that conducts impulses away from a __________.</display>
      <response>neuron cell body</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A bipolar __________ is a __________ with two processes extending from the cell body.</display>
      <response>neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An __________ is a neuroglia that line spaces in the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>ependyma</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An ependyma is a __________ that line spaces in the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>neuroglia</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The peripheral nervous system is the portion of the nervous system that consists of the __________ branching from the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>nerves</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A saltatory conduction is an impulse conduction in which the impulse seems to jump from __________ to __________ along the axon.</display>
      <response>node</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A saltatory conduction is an impulse conduction in which the impulse seems to jump from node to node along the __________.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A saltatory conduction is an __________ in which the impulse seems to jump from node to node along the axon.</display>
      <response>impulse conduction</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A sensory neuron is a neuron that can be stimulated by a __________ and conducts impulses into the brain or spinal cord.</display>
      <response>sensory receptor</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unipolar means a __________ with only one process extending from the cell body.</display>
      <response>neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ oversees all that we do and determines who we are.</display>
      <response>nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Through a __________ of cells and the information that they send and receive, the nervous system can detect changes affecting the body, make decisions, and stimulate muscles or glands to respond.</display>
      <response>vast communicating network</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A longer process called an axon, or nerve fiber, carries the information away from the cell in the form of __________, called impulses, which allow the neuron to communicate with other neurons and with cells outside the nervous system.</display>
      <response>bioelectric signals</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A longer process called an __________, or nerve fiber, carries the information away from the cell in the form of bioelectric signals, called impulses, which allow the neuron to communicate with other neurons and with cells outside the nervous system.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Typically, __________ within the nervous system are not isolated, but bundled in groups.</display>
      <response>axons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the peripheral nervous system, such bundles of __________ are called nerves.</display>
      <response>axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the __________, such bundles of axons are called nerves.</display>
      <response>peripheral nervous system</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the peripheral nervous system, __________ of axons are called nerves.</display>
      <response>such bundles</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The cells that form capillaries in the brain, in contrast, are much more tightly connected, thanks partly to neuroglia called __________.</display>
      <response>astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The cells that form capillaries in the brain, in contrast, are much more tightly connected, thanks partly to __________ called astrocytes.</display>
      <response>neuroglia</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ must consider the barrier when formulating drugs that act in the brain, including chemicals that let the drug through.</display>
      <response>Drug developers</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An important part of the nervous system at the cellular level is not a cell at all, but the functional connection between a neuron and the cell with which it communicates, called a __________.</display>
      <response>synapse</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Much of the work of the nervous system is to send and receive chemical messages at __________.</display>
      <response>synapses</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>One group, consisting of the brain and spinal cord, forms the __________.</display>
      <response>central nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The other group, the __________, includes the nerves that connect the central nervous system to other body parts.</display>
      <response>peripheral nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ also includes ganglia, which are clusters of neuron cell bodies located outside the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>PNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The PNS also includes __________, which are clusters of neuron cell bodies located outside the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>ganglia</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The three general functions of the nervous system -- receiving information, deciding what to do, and acting on those decisions -- are termed sensory, integrative, and __________.</display>
      <response>motor</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Structures called sensory receptors at the ends of neurons in the __________ provide the sensory function of the nervous system.</display>
      <response>peripheral nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These __________ gather information by detecting changes inside and outside the body.</display>
      <response>receptors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Sensory receptors convert their information into impulses, which are then conducted along peripheral nerves to the __________.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Sensory receptors convert their information into impulses, which are then conducted along __________ to the CNS.</display>
      <response>peripheral nerves</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurons that conduct impulses from the __________ to responsive structures called effectors carry out the motor functions of the nervous system.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurons that conduct impulses from the CNS to responsive structures called __________ carry out the motor functions of the nervous system.</display>
      <response>effectors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These __________ are outside the nervous system and include muscles and glands whose actions are either controlled or modified by nerve activity.</display>
      <response>effectors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The somatic nervous system communicates voluntary instructions originating in the __________ to skeletal muscles, causing contraction.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The somatic nervous system communicates voluntary instructions originating in the CNS to __________, causing contraction.</display>
      <response>skeletal muscles</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The somatic nervous system communicates voluntary instructions originating in the CNS to skeletal muscles, causing __________.</display>
      <response>contraction</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The somatic nervous system communicates __________ originating in the CNS to skeletal muscles, causing contraction.</display>
      <response>voluntary instructions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The autonomic nervous system communicates instructions from the CNS that control viscera, such as the heart and various glands, and thus causes __________.</display>
      <response>involuntary , subconscious actions</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The autonomic nervous system communicates instructions from the CNS that control __________, such as the heart and various glands, and thus causes involuntary, subconscious actions.</display>
      <response>viscera</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The autonomic nervous system communicates instructions from the __________ that control viscera, such as the heart and various glands, and thus causes involuntary, subconscious actions.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A network of fine threads called __________ extends into the axon and supports it.</display>
      <response>neurofilaments</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A network of fine threads called neurofilaments extends into the __________ and supports it.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Near the center of the neuron cell body is a __________ with a conspicuous nucleolus.</display>
      <response>large , spherical nucleus</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Near the center of the neuron cell body is a large, spherical nucleus with a __________.</display>
      <response>conspicuous nucleolus</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Near the center of the __________ cell body is a large, spherical nucleus with a conspicuous nucleolus.</display>
      <response>neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The cytoplasm of the axon includes many mitochondria, microtubules, and __________.</display>
      <response>neurofibrils</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The cytoplasm of the axon includes many mitochondria, __________, and neurofibrils.</display>
      <response>microtubules</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The cytoplasm of the __________ includes many mitochondria, microtubules, and neurofibrils.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The cytoplasm of the axon includes many __________, microtubules, and neurofibrils.</display>
      <response>mitochondria</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Near its end, an axon may have __________, each with a specialized ending called an axon terminal.</display>
      <response>many fine extensions</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Near its end, an axon may have many fine extensions, each with a specialized ending called an __________.</display>
      <response>axon terminal</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The general pattern is that neurons receive input through the __________ and the cell body, and send output in the form of an impulse conducted away from the cell body, down the axon.</display>
      <response>dendrites</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In this activity, called axonal transport, movement occurs in both directions between the cell body and the ends of the __________.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the PNS, neuroglia called Schwann cells encase the large axons of peripheral neurons in __________.</display>
      <response>lipid-rich sheaths</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the __________, neuroglia called Schwann cells encase the large axons of peripheral neurons in lipid-rich sheaths.</display>
      <response>PNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the PNS, __________ called Schwann cells encase the large axons of peripheral neurons in lipid-rich sheaths.</display>
      <response>neuroglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the PNS, neuroglia called __________ encase the large axons of peripheral neurons in lipid-rich sheaths.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the PNS, neuroglia called Schwann cells encase the __________ of peripheral neurons in lipid-rich sheaths.</display>
      <response>large axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the PNS, neuroglia called Schwann cells encase the large axons of __________ in lipid-rich sheaths.</display>
      <response>peripheral neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Myelin gives the cell membranes of __________ a higher proportion of lipid than other cell membranes.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ gives the cell membranes of Schwann cells a higher proportion of lipid than other cell membranes.</display>
      <response>Myelin</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Myelin gives the cell membranes of Schwann cells a higher proportion of __________ than other cell membranes.</display>
      <response>lipid</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The parts of the Schwann cells that contain most of the cytoplasm and the nuclei remain outside the myelin sheath and comprise a __________, or neurilemmal sheath, which surrounds the myelin sheath.</display>
      <response>neurilemma</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The parts of the __________ that contain most of the cytoplasm and the nuclei remain outside the myelin sheath and comprise a neurilemma, or neurilemmal sheath, which surrounds the myelin sheath.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The parts of the Schwann cells that contain most of the cytoplasm and the nuclei remain outside the __________ and comprise a neurilemma, or neurilemmal sheath, which surrounds the __________.</display>
      <response>myelin sheath</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Axons that have myelin sheaths are called myelinated axons, and those that do not have these sheaths are __________.</display>
      <response>unmyelinated axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Axons that have myelin sheaths are called __________, and those that do not have these sheaths are unmyelinated axons.</display>
      <response>myelinated axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Axons that have __________ are called myelinated axons, and those that do not have these sheaths are unmyelinated axons.</display>
      <response>myelin sheaths</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ that have myelin sheaths are called myelinated axons, and those that do not have these sheaths are unmyelinated axons.</display>
      <response>Axons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The white matter in the brain and spinal cord gets its color from masses of __________.</display>
      <response>myelinated axons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the CNS, myelin is produced by a type of neuroglia called an __________ rather than by a Schwann cell.</display>
      <response>oligodendrocyte</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the CNS, myelin is produced by a type of __________ called an oligodendrocyte rather than by a Schwann cell.</display>
      <response>neuroglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the CNS, myelin is produced by a type of neuroglia called an oligodendrocyte rather than by a __________.</display>
      <response>Schwann cell</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the __________, myelin is produced by a type of neuroglia called an oligodendrocyte rather than by a Schwann cell.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Clinical Application 10.2 discusses multiple __________, a condition in which neurons in the brain and spinal cord lose their myelin.</display>
      <response>sclerosis</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A __________ has many processes arising from its cell body.</display>
      <response>multipolar neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some __________ are in ganglia associated with the autonomic nervous system.</display>
      <response>multipolar neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some multipolar neurons are in __________ associated with the autonomic nervous system.</display>
      <response>ganglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some multipolar neurons are in ganglia associated with the __________.</display>
      <response>autonomic nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ are found in specialized parts of the eyes, nose, and ears.</display>
      <response>Bipolar neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Each __________ has a single process extending from its cell body.</display>
      <response>unipolar neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These are also called pseudounipolar, because they start out with __________ that merge into one during development.</display>
      <response>two processes</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A short distance from the cell body, this process divides into two branches, which really function as a single axon : One branch has __________ near a peripheral body part.</display>
      <response>dendrites</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurons can also be classified by functional differences into the following groups, depending on whether they carry information into the __________, completely within the __________, or out of the __________.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Sensory neurons conduct impulses from __________ into the brain or spinal cord.</display>
      <response>peripheral body parts</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>At their __________, the dendrites of these neurons or specialized structures associated with them act as sensory receptors, detecting changes in the outside world or in the body.</display>
      <response>distal ends</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>At their distal ends, the __________ of these neurons or specialized structures associated with them act as sensory receptors, detecting changes in the outside world or in the body.</display>
      <response>dendrites</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When sufficiently stimulated, sensory receptors trigger impulses that travel on __________ into the brain or spinal cord.</display>
      <response>sensory neuron axons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ relay information from one part of the brain or spinal cord to another.</display>
      <response>Interneurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, when motor neurons stimulate muscle cells, the muscle cells contract ; when motor neurons stimulate glands, the glands release __________.</display>
      <response>secretions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ are the most common type of neuron in the brain and spinal cord ; also found in ganglia of the autonomic nervous system.</display>
      <response>Multipolar neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Multipolar neurons are the most common type of neuron in the brain and spinal cord ; also found in __________ of the autonomic nervous system.</display>
      <response>ganglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Multipolar neurons are the most common type of neuron in the brain and spinal cord ; also found in ganglia of the __________.</display>
      <response>autonomic nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ have a cell body with a single process that divides into two branches and functions as an axon.</display>
      <response>Unipolar neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unipolar neurons have a cell body with a single process that divides into two branches and functions as an __________.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ replay information between neurons in the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>Interneurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Interneurons __________ between neurons in the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>replay information</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Motor neurons conduct impulses from the brain or spinal cord out to __________ -- muscles or glands.</display>
      <response>effectors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ were once thought to be mere bystanders to neural function, providing scaffolding and controlling the sites at which neurons contact one another.</display>
      <response>Neuroglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neuroglia were once thought to be mere bystanders to neural function, providing __________ and controlling the sites at which neurons contact one another.</display>
      <response>scaffolding</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ also produce the growth factors that nourish neurons and remove excess ions and neurotransmitters that accumulate between neurons.</display>
      <response>Neuroglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neuroglia also produce the growth factors that nourish neurons and remove excess ions and __________ that accumulate between neurons.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitters</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In cell culture experiments, certain types of __________ to form and maintain synapses.</display>
      <response>neuroglia signal neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In cell culture experiments, certain types of neuroglia signal neurons to form and maintain __________.</display>
      <response>synapses</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The four types of CNS neuroglia are __________, oligodendrocytes, microglia, and ependyma : As their name implies, __________ are star-shaped cells.</display>
      <response>astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The four types of CNS neuroglia are astrocytes, oligodendrocytes, __________, and ependyma : As their name implies, astrocytes are star-shaped cells.</display>
      <response>microglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The four types of CNS neuroglia are astrocytes, __________, microglia, and ependyma : As their name implies, astrocytes are star-shaped cells.</display>
      <response>oligodendrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The four types of __________ are astrocytes, oligodendrocytes, microglia, and ependyma : As their name implies, astrocytes are star-shaped cells.</display>
      <response>CNS neuroglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The four types of CNS neuroglia are astrocytes, oligodendrocytes, microglia, and ependyma : As their name implies, astrocytes are __________.</display>
      <response>star-shaped cells</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ also respond to injury of brain tissue and form a special type of scar tissue, which fills spaces and closes gaps in the CNS.</display>
      <response>Astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Astrocytes also respond to injury of brain tissue and form a special type of scar tissue, which fills spaces and closes gaps in the __________.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Astrocytes also respond to injury of brain tissue and form a special type of scar tissue, which fills spaces and closes __________ in the CNS.</display>
      <response>gaps</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ play a role in the formation of the blood-brain barrier, which restricts movement of substances between the blood and the CNS.</display>
      <response>Astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Astrocytes play a role in the formation of the __________, which restricts movement of substances between the blood and the CNS.</display>
      <response>blood-brain barrier</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Astrocytes play a role in the formation of the blood-brain barrier, which restricts movement of substances between the blood and the __________.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Gap junctions link astrocytes to one another, forming __________ through which calcium ions travel, possibly stimulating neurons.</display>
      <response>protein-lined channels</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Gap junctions link __________ to one another, forming protein-lined channels through which calcium ions travel, possibly stimulating neurons.</display>
      <response>astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ link astrocytes to one another, forming protein-lined channels through which calcium ions travel, possibly stimulating neurons.</display>
      <response>Gap junctions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unlike the Schwann cells of the PNS, __________ can send out a number of processes, each of which forms a myelin sheath around a nearby axon.</display>
      <response>oligodendrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unlike the Schwann cells of the __________, oligodendrocytes can send out a number of processes, each of which forms a myelin sheath around a nearby axon.</display>
      <response>PNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unlike the __________ of the PNS, oligodendrocytes can send out a number of processes, each of which forms a myelin sheath around a nearby axon.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unlike the Schwann cells of the PNS, oligodendrocytes can send out a number of processes, each of which forms a __________ around a nearby axon.</display>
      <response>myelin sheath</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Unlike the Schwann cells of the PNS, oligodendrocytes can send out a number of processes, each of which forms a myelin sheath around a __________.</display>
      <response>nearby axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These cells are scattered throughout the CNS, where they help support neurons and __________ bacterial cells and cellular debris.</display>
      <response>phagocytize</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These cells are scattered throughout the __________, where they help support neurons and phagocytize bacterial cells and cellular debris.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>They usually proliferate whenever the brain or spinal __________ is inflamed because of injury or disease.</display>
      <response>cord</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>They form the __________ of the central canal that extends downward through the spinal cord.</display>
      <response>inner lining</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>They form the inner lining of the central canal that extends downward through the __________.</display>
      <response>spinal cord</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependymal cells also form a __________ that covers the inside of spaces in the brain called ventricles.</display>
      <response>one-cell-thick epithelial-like membrane</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ also form a one-cell-thick epithelial-like membrane that covers the inside of spaces in the brain called ventricles.</display>
      <response>Ependymal cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependymal cells also form a one-cell-thick epithelial-like membrane that covers the inside of spaces in the brain called __________.</display>
      <response>ventricles</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Here, gap junctions join __________, allowing free exchange between cells.</display>
      <response>ependymal cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Here, __________ join ependymal cells, allowing free exchange between cells.</display>
      <response>gap junctions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ itself is porous, allowing substances to diffuse freely between the interstitial fluid of the brain tissues and the fluid in the ventricles.</display>
      <response>ependymal layer</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The ependymal layer itself is porous, allowing substances to diffuse freely between the __________ of the brain tissues and the fluid in the ventricles.</display>
      <response>interstitial fluid</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The ependymal layer itself is porous, allowing substances to diffuse freely between the interstitial fluid of the brain tissues and the fluid in the __________.</display>
      <response>ventricles</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependymal cells also cover the specialized capillaries called __________ associated with the ventricles of the brain.</display>
      <response>choroid plexuses</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ also cover the specialized capillaries called choroid plexuses associated with the ventricles of the brain.</display>
      <response>Ependymal cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependymal cells also cover the specialized capillaries called choroid plexuses associated with the __________ of the brain.</display>
      <response>ventricles</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________, which comprise more than half of the volume of the brain and outnumber neurons 10 to 1, are critical to neuron function.</display>
      <response>Neuroglia</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In one familial form of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, __________ release a toxin that destroys motor neurons, causing progressive weakness.</display>
      <response>astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In __________ of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, astrocytes release a toxin that destroys motor neurons, causing progressive weakness.</display>
      <response>one familial form</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In one familial form of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, astrocytes release a __________ that destroys motor neurons, causing progressive weakness.</display>
      <response>toxin</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In Huntington disease, which causes uncontrollable movements and cognitive impairment, __________ in the brain release a toxin that damages neurons.</display>
      <response>microglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In __________, which causes uncontrollable movements and cognitive impairment, microglia in the brain release a toxin that damages neurons.</display>
      <response>Huntington disease</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In Huntington disease, which causes __________ and cognitive impairment, microglia in the brain release a toxin that damages neurons.</display>
      <response>uncontrollable movements</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In Huntington disease, which causes uncontrollable movements and cognitive impairment, microglia in the brain release a __________ that damages neurons.</display>
      <response>toxin</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In Huntington disease, which causes uncontrollable movements and cognitive __________, microglia in the brain release a toxin that damages neurons.</display>
      <response>impairment</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The two types of __________ in the peripheral nervous system are Schwann cells and satellite cells : Schwann cells produce the myelin on peripheral myelinated neurons, as described earlier.</display>
      <response>neuroglia</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The two types of neuroglia in the peripheral nervous system are __________ and satellite cells : __________ produce the myelin on peripheral myelinated neurons, as described earlier.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The two types of neuroglia in the peripheral nervous system are Schwann cells and satellite cells : Schwann cells produce the myelin on __________, as described earlier.</display>
      <response>peripheral myelinated neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The two types of neuroglia in the __________ are Schwann cells and satellite cells : Schwann cells produce the myelin on peripheral myelinated neurons, as described earlier.</display>
      <response>peripheral nervous system</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Satellite cells provide nutritional support and help regulate the __________ of ions around neuron cell bodies within ganglia.</display>
      <response>concentrations</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Satellite cells provide nutritional support and help regulate the concentrations of ions around __________ within ganglia.</display>
      <response>neuron cell bodies</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ provide nutritional support and help regulate the concentrations of ions around neuron cell bodies within ganglia.</display>
      <response>Satellite cells</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ have the following functions : structural support, formation of scar tissue, transport of substances between blood vessels and neurons, communication with one another and with neurons, mopping up excess ions and neurotransmitters, inducing synapse formation.</display>
      <response>Astrocytes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Astrocytes have the following functions : structural support, formation of scar tissue, transport of substances between blood vessels and neurons, communication with one another and with neurons, mopping up excess ions and __________, inducing synapse formation.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitters</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Astrocytes have the following functions : structural support, formation of scar tissue, transport of substances between blood vessels and neurons, communication with one another and with neurons, mopping up excess ions and neurotransmitters, inducing __________.</display>
      <response>synapse formation</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependyma form a porous layer through which substances diffuse between the interstitial fluid of the brain and spinal cord and the __________.</display>
      <response>cerebrospinal fluid</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependyma form a porous layer through which substances diffuse between the __________ of the brain and spinal cord and the cerebrospinal fluid.</display>
      <response>interstitial fluid</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ependyma form a __________ through which substances diffuse between the interstitial fluid of the brain and spinal cord and the cerebrospinal fluid.</display>
      <response>porous layer</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Schwann cells are cells with __________ that wrap tightly around the axons of peripheral neurons.</display>
      <response>abundant , lipid-rich membranes</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ are cells with abundant, lipid-rich membranes that wrap tightly around the axons of peripheral neurons.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Schwann cells are cells with abundant, lipid-rich membranes that wrap tightly around the __________ of peripheral neurons.</display>
      <response>axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Schwann cells are cells with abundant, lipid-rich membranes that wrap tightly around the axons of __________.</display>
      <response>peripheral neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Satellite cells are __________ that surround cell bodies of neurons in ganglia.</display>
      <response>small , cuboidal cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Satellite cells are small, cuboidal cells that surround cell bodies of __________ in ganglia.</display>
      <response>neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ are small, cuboidal cells that surround cell bodies of neurons in ganglia.</display>
      <response>Satellite cells</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Injury to the cell body usually kills the neuron, and because mature neurons do not divide, the destroyed cell is not replaced unless __________ are stimulated to proliferate.</display>
      <response>neural stem cells</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if injury or disease separates an axon in a peripheral nerve from its cell body, the distal portion of the axon and its myelin sheath deteriorate within a few weeks, although the Schwann cells and __________ remain.</display>
      <response>neurilemma</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if injury or disease separates an axon in a peripheral nerve from its cell body, the distal portion of the axon and its myelin sheath deteriorate within a few weeks, although the __________ and neurilemma remain.</display>
      <response>Schwann cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if injury or disease separates an axon in a peripheral nerve from its cell body, the distal portion of the axon and its __________ deteriorate within a few weeks, although the Schwann cells and neurilemma remain.</display>
      <response>myelin sheath</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if injury or disease separates an axon in a peripheral nerve from its cell body, the __________ of the axon and its myelin sheath deteriorate within a few weeks, although the Schwann cells and neurilemma remain.</display>
      <response>distal portion</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if injury or disease separates an axon in a __________ from its cell body, the distal portion of the axon and its myelin sheath deteriorate within a few weeks, although the Schwann cells and neurilemma remain.</display>
      <response>peripheral nerve</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if injury or disease separates an __________ in a peripheral nerve from its cell body, the distal portion of the __________ and its myelin sheath deteriorate within a few weeks, although the Schwann cells and neurilemma remain.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If an axon of a neuron within the CNS is separated from its cell body, the distal portion of the axon will degenerate, but more slowly than a separated axon in the __________.</display>
      <response>PNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If an axon of a neuron within the __________ is separated from its cell body, the distal portion of the axon will degenerate, but more slowly than a separated axon in the PNS.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If an axon of a neuron within the CNS is separated from its cell body, the __________ of the axon will degenerate, but more slowly than a separated axon in the PNS.</display>
      <response>distal portion</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Consequently, the __________ of a damaged axon that begins to grow has no tube of sheath cells to guide it.</display>
      <response>proximal end</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Consequently, the proximal end of a damaged axon that begins to grow has no tube of __________ to guide it.</display>
      <response>sheath cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Consequently, the proximal end of a damaged __________ that begins to grow has no tube of sheath cells to guide it.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>New neural tissue arises from neural stem cells, which give rise to __________ that can give rise to neurons or neuroglia.</display>
      <response>neural progenitor cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>New neural tissue arises from __________, which give rise to neural progenitor cells that can give rise to neurons or neuroglia.</display>
      <response>neural stem cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>New __________ arises from neural stem cells, which give rise to neural progenitor cells that can give rise to neurons or neuroglia.</display>
      <response>neural tissue</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>New neural tissue arises from neural stem cells, which give rise to neural progenitor cells that can give rise to __________ or neuroglia.</display>
      <response>neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The neuron receiving input at the synapse is the __________.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic neuron</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The neuron receiving input at the __________ is the postsynaptic neuron.</display>
      <response>synapse</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The mechanism by which the impulse in the __________ the postsynaptic cell is called synaptic transmission.</display>
      <response>presynaptic neuron signals</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The mechanism by which the impulse in the presynaptic neuron signals the __________ is called synaptic transmission.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic cell</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The mechanism by which the __________ in the presynaptic neuron signals the postsynaptic cell is called synaptic transmission.</display>
      <response>impulse</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ by which the impulse in the presynaptic neuron signals the postsynaptic cell is called synaptic transmission.</display>
      <response>mechanism</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The increased calcium concentration inside the cell initiates a series of events that fuses the __________ with the cell membrane, where they release their neurotransmitter by exocytosis.</display>
      <response>synaptic vesicles</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The increased calcium concentration inside the cell initiates a series of events that fuses the synaptic vesicles with the cell membrane, where they release their __________ by exocytosis.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitter</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Once the neurotransmitter binds to receptors on a __________, the action is either excitatory or inhibitory.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic cell</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Once the __________ binds to receptors on a postsynaptic cell, the action is either excitatory or inhibitory.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitter</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Once the neurotransmitter binds to __________ on a postsynaptic cell, the action is either excitatory or inhibitory.</display>
      <response>receptors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>This __________ is due to an unequal distribution of positive and negative ions across the membrane.</display>
      <response>polarization</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>This polarization is due to an __________ of positive and negative ions across the membrane.</display>
      <response>unequal distribution</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The distribution is created largely by the __________, which actively transports sodium ions out of the cell and potassium ions into the cell.</display>
      <response>sodium/potassium pump</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>It is also in part due to channels in the cell membrane that determine __________ to these ions.</display>
      <response>membrane permeability</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Thus, even though __________ are present for sodium and potassium, the ability of these ions to diffuse across the cell membrane depends on the presence of channels.</display>
      <response>concentration gradients</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For an ion to diffuse across the cell membrane requires __________ for that ion and membrane permeability to that ion.</display>
      <response>both a concentration gradient</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For an ion to diffuse across the cell membrane requires both a concentration gradient for that ion and __________ to that ion.</display>
      <response>membrane permeability</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Also, the cytoplasm of these cells has many negatively charged ions, which include __________, sulfate, and proteins, that are synthesized inside the cell and can not diffuse through cell membranes.</display>
      <response>phosphate</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Because of the gradients and __________ for Na + and K +, we would expect potassium to diffuse out of the cell more rapidly than sodium could diffuse in.</display>
      <response>permeabilities</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Because of the __________ and permeabilities for Na + and K +, we would expect potassium to diffuse out of the cell more rapidly than sodium could diffuse in.</display>
      <response>gradients</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Because of the gradients and permeabilities for __________ + and K +, we would expect potassium to diffuse out of the cell more rapidly than sodium could diffuse in.</display>
      <response>Na</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As a result, the outside of the membrane gains a __________ of positive charges, and the inside reflects a surplus of the impermeant negatively charged ions.</display>
      <response>slight surplus</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A number of mechanisms move ions across cell membranes, but for our purposes we will consider the __________ + / K + pump responsible for maintaining this balance.</display>
      <response>Na</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Thus, the cell continues to expend metabolic energy in the form of ATP to actively transport sodium and potassium ions in opposite directions, thereby maintaining the __________ for those ions responsible for their diffusion in the first place.</display>
      <response>concentration gradients</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the case of a resting neuron, one that is not sending impulses or responding to other neurons, the membrane potential is termed the resting potential and for a __________ has a value of -LSB-? -RSB-</display>
      <response>typical neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>To understand how the resting potential provides the energy for sending an impulse down the __________, we must first understand how neurons respond to signals called stimuli.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>With the resting membrane potential established, sodium ions and __________ continue to diffuse across the cell membrane.</display>
      <response>potassium ions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The negative membrane potential helps the positively charged sodium ions enter the cell despite sodium's low permeability, but it hinders the positively charged potassium ions from leaving the cell despite __________.</display>
      <response>potassium's higher permeability</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The negative membrane potential helps the positively charged sodium ions enter the cell despite __________, but it hinders the positively charged potassium ions from leaving the cell despite potassium's higher permeability.</display>
      <response>sodium's low permeability</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The net effect is that three sodium __________ into the cell for every two potassium ions that leak out.</display>
      <response>ions leak</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The Na + / K + pump balances these leaks by pumping three sodium ions out for every two potassium ions it pumps in.</display>
      <response>K + pump balances</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ + / K + pump balances these leaks by pumping three sodium ions out for every two potassium ions it pumps in.</display>
      <response>Na</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The Na + / K + pump balances these __________ by pumping three sodium ions out for every two potassium ions it pumps in.</display>
      <response>leaks</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The key to understanding how this happens is the action potential, which is a rapid change in the __________, first in a positive direction, then in a negative direction, returning to the resting potential.</display>
      <response>membrane potential</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When a neuron conducts an electrical current, that current is in the form of a series of __________ occurring in sequence along the axon, from the cell body to the axon terminal.</display>
      <response>action potentials</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ are excitable ; that is, they can respond to changes in their surroundings.</display>
      <response>Neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some __________, for example, detect changes in temperature, light, or pressure outside the body, whereas others respond to signals from inside the body.</display>
      <response>neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In either case, such changes or __________ usually affect the membrane potential in the region of the membrane exposed to the stimulus, causing a local potential change.</display>
      <response>stimuli</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If, as a result, the __________ potential becomes more negative than the resting potential, the __________ is hyperpolarized.</display>
      <response>membrane</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If the __________ becomes less negative than the resting potential, the __________ is depolarized.</display>
      <response>membrane</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if the membrane is being depolarized, the greater the stimulus, the greater the __________.</display>
      <response>depolarization</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The mechanism uses another type of ion channel, a __________ that opens when threshold is reached.</display>
      <response>voltage-gated sodium channel</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The mechanism uses another type of ion channel, a voltage-gated sodium channel that opens when __________ is reached.</display>
      <response>threshold</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The mechanism uses another type of __________, a voltage-gated sodium channel that opens when threshold is reached.</display>
      <response>ion channel</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In a __________, the first part of the axon, the cone-shaped axon hillock or initial segment, is often referred to as the trigger zone because it contains many such voltage-gated sodium channels.</display>
      <response>multipolar neuron</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In a multipolar neuron, the first part of the axon, the cone-shaped axon hillock or initial segment, is often referred to as the trigger zone because it contains __________.</display>
      <response>many such voltage-gated sodium channels</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In a multipolar neuron, the first part of the axon, the __________ or initial segment, is often referred to as the trigger zone because it contains many such voltage-gated sodium channels.</display>
      <response>cone-shaped axon hillock</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>At the resting membrane potential, these sodium channels remain closed, but when threshold is reached, they open for an instant, briefly increasing __________.</display>
      <response>sodium permeability</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>At the resting membrane potential, these sodium channels remain closed, but when __________ is reached, they open for an instant, briefly increasing sodium permeability.</display>
      <response>threshold</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>At the resting membrane potential, these __________ remain closed, but when threshold is reached, they open for an instant, briefly increasing sodium permeability.</display>
      <response>sodium channels</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Sodium ions diffuse inward through the open sodium channels, down their __________, aided by the attraction of the sodium ions to the negative charges on the inside of the membrane.</display>
      <response>concentration gradient</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As the sodium ions diffuse inward, the membrane potential at the __________ from its resting value and momentarily becomes positive on the inside.</display>
      <response>trigger zone changes</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ quickly close, but at almost the same time, slower voltage-gated potassium channels open and briefly increase potassium permeability.</display>
      <response>voltage-gated sodium channels</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The voltage-gated sodium channels quickly __________, slower voltage-gated potassium channels open and briefly increase potassium permeability.</display>
      <response>close , but at almost the same time</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The voltage-gated sodium channels quickly close, but at almost the same time, __________ open and briefly increase potassium permeability.</display>
      <response>slower voltage-gated potassium channels</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The voltage-gated sodium channels quickly close, but at almost the same time, slower voltage-gated potassium channels open and briefly __________.</display>
      <response>increase potassium permeability</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The voltage-gated sodium channels quickly close, but at almost the same time, slower voltage-gated potassium channels open and __________ increase potassium permeability.</display>
      <response>briefly</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As potassium ions diffuse outward, down their __________ and through the open potassium channels, the inside becomes negatively charged once more.</display>
      <response>concentration gradient</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As __________ diffuse outward, down their concentration gradient and through the open potassium channels, the inside becomes negatively charged once more.</display>
      <response>potassium ions</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As potassium ions diffuse outward, down their concentration gradient and through the __________, the inside becomes negatively charged once more.</display>
      <response>open potassium channels</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The number of sodium and potassium ions crossing the membrane during an action potential is extremely small, although the __________ is quite significant.</display>
      <response>bioelectric effect</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ in a neuron are along the axon, especially at the trigger zone.</display>
      <response>Most voltage-gated channels</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Most voltage-gated channels in a neuron are along the __________, especially at the trigger zone.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An action potential at the trigger zone causes a bioelectric current to flow a short distance down the __________, which stimulates the adjacent membrane to reach its threshold level, triggering another action potential.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The second action potential causes another electric current to flow farther down the __________.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>This sequence of events results in the conduction of the action potential along the __________ without decreasing in amplitude, even if the __________ branches.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ of an action potential continues to the end of the axon.</display>
      <response>propagation</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The propagation of an action potential continues to the end of the __________.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Conduction of an impulse along an __________ is similar to conduction of an impulse in a muscle fiber mentioned in section 9.2, Skeletal Muscle Contraction, Stimulus for Contraction.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Conduction of an impulse along an axon is similar to __________ of an impulse in a muscle fiber mentioned in section 9.2, Skeletal Muscle Contraction, Stimulus for Contraction.</display>
      <response>conduction</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ of an impulse along an axon is similar to conduction of an impulse in a muscle fiber mentioned in section 9.2, Skeletal Muscle Contraction, Stimulus for Contraction.</display>
      <response>Conduction</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the muscle fiber, stimulation at the motor end plate triggers an action potential that spreads over the surface of the fiber and down into its __________.</display>
      <response>transverse tubules</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the muscle fiber, __________ at the motor end plate triggers an action potential that spreads over the surface of the fiber and down into its transverse tubules.</display>
      <response>stimulation</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Nerve cell membrane maintains resting potential by diffusion of Na + and K + down their __________ as the cell pumps them up the gradients.</display>
      <response>concentration gradients</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Nerve cell membrane maintains resting potential by diffusion of __________ + and K + down their concentration gradients as the cell pumps them up the gradients.</display>
      <response>Na</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ diffuse inward, depolarizing the membrane.</display>
      <response>Sodium ions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ diffuse outward, repolarizing the membrane.</display>
      <response>Potassium ions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The resulting action potential causes an electric current that stimulates __________ of the membrane.</display>
      <response>adjacent portions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In other words, if a __________ responds at all, it responds completely.</display>
      <response>neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Thus, an impulse is conducted whenever a stimulus of threshold intensity or above is applied to an __________ and all impulses conducted on that __________ are the same strength.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Thus, an impulse is conducted whenever a stimulus of __________ or above is applied to an axon and all impulses conducted on that axon are the same strength.</display>
      <response>threshold intensity</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The number of action potentials per second that an __________ can generate is limited, because during an action potential, that part of the __________ becomes unresponsive to another threshold stimulus.</display>
      <response>axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>This brief period, called the __________, has two parts.</display>
      <response>refractory period</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A __________ follows, as the membrane reestablishes its resting potential.</display>
      <response>relative refractory period</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Remembering that the action potential takes about a millisecond, and adding the time of the __________, the maximum theoretical frequency of impulses in a neuron is about 700 per second.</display>
      <response>relative refractory period</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the body, this limit is rarely achieved -- __________ of about 100 impulses per second are common.</display>
      <response>frequencies</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The __________ also ensures that an action potential is conducted in only one direction, down the axon, because the area upstream from where the action potential has just occurred is still in the __________ from the previous action potential.</display>
      <response>refractory period</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Thus, myelin prevents almost all flow of ions through the membrane that it encloses and serves as an __________.</display>
      <response>electrical insulator</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>It might seem that the __________ would prevent conduction of an impulse, and this would be true if the sheath were continuous along the length of the axon.</display>
      <response>myelin sheath</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When a __________ is stimulated to threshold, an action potential occurs at the trigger zone.</display>
      <response>myelinated axon</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As this local current reaches the first node, it stimulates the membrane to its threshold level, and an action potential occurs there, sending a bioelectric current to the __________ downstream.</display>
      <response>next node</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As this local current reaches the __________, it stimulates the membrane to its threshold level, and an action potential occurs there, sending a bioelectric current to the next node downstream.</display>
      <response>first node</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Consequently, as an impulse is conducted along a __________, action potentials occur only at the nodes.</display>
      <response>myelinated axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Consequently, as an impulse is conducted along a myelinated axon, __________ occur only at the nodes.</display>
      <response>action potentials</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Consequently, as an impulse is conducted along a myelinated axon, action potentials occur only at the __________.</display>
      <response>nodes</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Because the __________ appear to jump from node to node, this type of impulse conduction is called saltatory conduction.</display>
      <response>action potentials</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Because the action potentials appear to jump from node to node, this type of __________ is called saltatory conduction.</display>
      <response>impulse conduction</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Conduction on myelinated axons is many times faster than conduction on __________ The diameter of the axon affects the speed of impulse conduction -- the greater the diameter, the faster the impulse.</display>
      <response>unmyelinated axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Conduction on __________ is many times faster than conduction on unmyelinated axons The diameter of the axon affects the speed of impulse conduction -- the greater the diameter, the faster the impulse.</display>
      <response>myelinated axons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An impulse on a comparatively __________, such as that of a motor neuron associated with a skeletal muscle, might travel 120 meters per second, whereas an impulse on a thin, unmyelinated axon, such as that of a sensory neuron associated with the skin, might move only 0.5 meter per second.</display>
      <response>thick , myelinated axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An impulse on a comparatively thick, myelinated axon, such as that of a motor neuron associated with a skeletal muscle, might travel 120 meters per second, whereas an impulse on a __________, such as that of a sensory neuron associated with the skin, might move only 0.5 meter per second.</display>
      <response>thin , unmyelinated axon</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>An impulse on a comparatively thick, myelinated axon, such as that of a motor neuron associated with a skeletal muscle, might travel 120 meters per second, whereas an impulse on a thin, unmyelinated axon, such as that of a sensory neuron associated with the skin, might move only __________ per second.</display>
      <response>0.5 meter</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When neurotransmitters bind these receptors, they cause ion channels in the __________ to open.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic cells</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When __________ bind these receptors, they cause ion channels in the postsynaptic cells to open.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitters</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When neurotransmitters bind these __________, they cause ion channels in the postsynaptic cells to open.</display>
      <response>receptors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ion channels that respond to neurotransmitter molecules are called chemically gated, in contrast to the __________ that participate in action potentials.</display>
      <response>voltage-gated ion channels</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ion channels that respond to __________ are called chemically gated, in contrast to the voltage-gated ion channels that participate in action potentials.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitter molecules</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Ion channels that respond to neurotransmitter molecules are called chemically gated, in contrast to the voltage-gated ion channels that participate in __________.</display>
      <response>action potentials</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ that respond to neurotransmitter molecules are called chemically gated, in contrast to the voltage-gated ion channels that participate in action potentials.</display>
      <response>Ion channels</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Changes in chemically gated ion channels create local potentials, called __________, which enable one neuron to affect another.</display>
      <response>synaptic potentials</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Changes in chemically gated ion channels create __________, called synaptic potentials, which enable one neuron to affect another.</display>
      <response>local potentials</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Changes in chemically gated ion channels create local potentials, called synaptic potentials, which enable __________ to affect another.</display>
      <response>one neuron</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Changes in chemically gated __________ create local potentials, called synaptic potentials, which enable one neuron to affect another.</display>
      <response>ion channels</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ that make reaching threshold less likely are called inhibitory, because they decrease the chance that an impulse will occur.</display>
      <response>Neurotransmitters</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurotransmitters that make reaching __________ less likely are called inhibitory, because they decrease the chance that an impulse will occur.</display>
      <response>threshold</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some relatively uncommon synapses, called __________, are in certain parts of the brain and eyes.</display>
      <response>electrical synapses</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some relatively __________, called electrical synapses, are in certain parts of the brain and eyes.</display>
      <response>uncommon synapses</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if a neurotransmitter binds to a __________ and opens sodium ion channels, the ions diffuse inward, depolarizing the membrane, possibly triggering an action potential.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic receptor</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if a __________ binds to a postsynaptic receptor and opens sodium ion channels, the ions diffuse inward, depolarizing the membrane, possibly triggering an action potential.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitter</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If a __________ binds other receptors and increases membrane permeability to potassium ions, these ions diffuse outward, hyperpolarizing the membrane.</display>
      <response>different neurotransmitter</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If a different neurotransmitter binds other receptors and increases __________ to potassium ions, these ions diffuse outward, hyperpolarizing the membrane.</display>
      <response>membrane permeability</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Because an action potential is now less likely to occur, this change is called an __________.</display>
      <response>inhibitory postsynaptic potential</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In this case, negative chloride ions enter the cell opposing the __________.</display>
      <response>depolarization</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the brain and spinal cord, each neuron may receive the __________ of a thousand or more axons on its dendrites and cell body.</display>
      <response>synaptic knobs</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the brain and spinal cord, each neuron may receive the synaptic knobs of a __________ on its dendrites and cell body.</display>
      <response>thousand or more axons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In the brain and spinal cord, each neuron may receive the synaptic knobs of a thousand or more axons on its __________ and cell body.</display>
      <response>dendrites</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Conversely, if the __________ is inhibitory, an action potential does not occur.</display>
      <response>net effect</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Summation of the excitatory and inhibitory effects of the __________ commonly takes place at the trigger zone.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic potentials</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ of the excitatory and inhibitory effects of the postsynaptic potentials commonly takes place at the trigger zone.</display>
      <response>Summation</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Summation of the __________ of the postsynaptic potentials commonly takes place at the trigger zone.</display>
      <response>excitatory and inhibitory effects</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Summation of the excitatory and inhibitory effects of the postsynaptic potentials commonly takes place at the __________.</display>
      <response>trigger zone</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>In this way, the trigger zone, as its name implies, serves as a __________ of the neuron.</display>
      <response>decision-making part</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Some __________ release only one type, whereas others produce two or three.</display>
      <response>neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurotransmitters include acetylcholine, which stimulates skeletal muscle contractions ; a group of compounds called __________, which are modified amino acids ; a group of unmodified amino acids ; and a large group of peptides, which are short chains of amino acids.</display>
      <response>monoamines</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ include acetylcholine, which stimulates skeletal muscle contractions ; a group of compounds called monoamines, which are modified amino acids ; a group of unmodified amino acids ; and a large group of peptides, which are short chains of amino acids.</display>
      <response>Neurotransmitters</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurotransmitters include __________, which stimulates skeletal muscle contractions ; a group of compounds called monoamines, which are modified amino acids ; a group of unmodified amino acids ; and a large group of peptides, which are short chains of amino acids.</display>
      <response>acetylcholine</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Neurotransmitters include acetylcholine, which stimulates __________ ; a group of compounds called monoamines, which are modified amino acids ; a group of unmodified amino acids ; and a large group of peptides, which are short chains of amino acids.</display>
      <response>skeletal muscle contractions</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When an action potential passes along the membrane of a synaptic knob, it increases the __________ to calcium ions by opening calcium ion channels.</display>
      <response>membrane's permeability</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>When an action potential passes along the membrane of a __________, it increases the membrane's permeability to calcium ions by opening calcium ion channels.</display>
      <response>synaptic knob</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Norepinephrine in the __________ may excite or inhibit autonomic nervous system actions, depending on receptors.</display>
      <response>PNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ in the PNS may excite or inhibit autonomic nervous system actions, depending on receptors.</display>
      <response>Norepinephrine</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Norepinephrine in the PNS may excite or inhibit __________, depending on receptors.</display>
      <response>autonomic nervous system actions</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Norepinephrine in the PNS may excite or inhibit autonomic nervous system actions, depending on __________.</display>
      <response>receptors</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ in the CNS creates a sense of well-being ; deficiency in some brain areas associated with Parkinson disease.</display>
      <response>Dopamine</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Dopamine in the __________ creates a sense of well-being ; deficiency in some brain areas associated with Parkinson disease.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Dopamine in the CNS creates a sense of well-being ; deficiency in some brain areas associated with __________.</display>
      <response>Parkinson disease</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ and endorphins in the CNS are generally inhibitory ; reduce pain by inhibiting substance P release.</display>
      <response>Enkephalins</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Enkephalins and endorphins in the __________ are generally inhibitory ; reduce pain by inhibiting substance P release.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Enkephalins and __________ in the CNS are generally inhibitory ; reduce pain by inhibiting substance P release.</display>
      <response>endorphins</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A __________ becomes part of the cell membrane after it releases its neurotransmitter.</display>
      <response>vesicle</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>A vesicle becomes part of the cell membrane after it releases its __________.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitter</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ eventually returns the membrane material to the cytoplasm, where it can provide material to form new secretory vesicles.</display>
      <response>Endocytosis</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Endocytosis eventually returns the membrane material to the cytoplasm, where it can provide material to form __________.</display>
      <response>new secretory vesicles</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Endocytosis eventually returns the membrane material to the __________, where it can provide material to form new secretory vesicles.</display>
      <response>cytoplasm</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These peptides act as neurotransmitters or as __________, which are substances that alter a neuron's response to a neurotransmitter or block the release of a neurotransmitter.</display>
      <response>neuromodulators</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These __________ act as neurotransmitters or as neuromodulators, which are substances that alter a neuron's response to a neurotransmitter or block the release of a neurotransmitter.</display>
      <response>peptides</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These peptides act as neurotransmitters or as neuromodulators, which are substances that alter a __________ to a neurotransmitter or block the release of a neurotransmitter.</display>
      <response>neuron's response</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These peptides act as __________ or as neuromodulators, which are substances that alter a neuron's response to a neurotransmitter or block the release of a neurotransmitter.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitters</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>These peptides act as neurotransmitters or as neuromodulators, which are substances that alter a neuron's response to a __________ or block the release of a __________.</display>
      <response>neurotransmitter</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ and endorphins may relieve pain by inhibiting the release of substance P from these neurons.</display>
      <response>Enkephalins</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Enkephalins and __________ may relieve pain by inhibiting the release of substance P from these neurons.</display>
      <response>endorphins</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Enkephalins and endorphins may relieve pain by inhibiting the release of substance P from these __________.</display>
      <response>neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>The way the nervous system collects, processes, and responds to information reflects, in part, the organization of __________ and axons in the brain and spinal cord.</display>
      <response>neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________, which are the neurons completely within the CNS, are organized into neuronal pools.</display>
      <response>Interneurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Interneurons, which are the neurons completely within the CNS, are organized into __________.</display>
      <response>neuronal pools</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Interneurons, which are the neurons completely within the __________, are organized into neuronal pools.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If the net effect is excitatory, __________ may be reached, and an impulse triggered.</display>
      <response>threshold</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>If the net effect is excitatory, but subthreshold, an __________ will not be triggered.</display>
      <response>impulse</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Repeated impulses on an __________ may cause that neuron to release more neurotransmitter in response to a single impulse, making it more likely to bring the postsynaptic cell to threshold.</display>
      <response>excitatory presynaptic neuron</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Repeated impulses on an excitatory presynaptic neuron may cause that neuron to release more neurotransmitter in response to a single impulse, making it more likely to bring the __________ to threshold.</display>
      <response>postsynaptic cell</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Repeated impulses on an excitatory presynaptic neuron may cause that neuron to release __________ in response to a single impulse, making it more likely to bring the postsynaptic cell to threshold.</display>
      <response>more neurotransmitter</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Repeated impulses on an excitatory presynaptic neuron may cause that neuron to release more neurotransmitter in response to a __________, making it more likely to bring the postsynaptic cell to threshold.</display>
      <response>single impulse</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>__________ makes it possible for a neuron to sum impulses from different sources.</display>
      <response>Convergence</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Convergence makes it possible for a __________ to sum impulses from different sources.</display>
      <response>neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if a neuron receives what would be subthreshold stimulation from one presynaptic neuron, it may reach threshold if it receives additional stimulation from __________ at the same time.</display>
      <response>one or more additional presynaptic neurons</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>For example, if a neuron receives what would be subthreshold stimulation from __________, it may reach threshold if it receives additional stimulation from one or more additional presynaptic neurons at the same time.</display>
      <response>one presynaptic neuron</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Therefore, a neuron of a __________ may exhibit divergence by forming synapses with several other neurons.</display>
      <response>neuronal pool</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Therefore, a neuron of a neuronal pool may exhibit __________ by forming synapses with several other neurons.</display>
      <response>divergence</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Therefore, a neuron of a neuronal pool may exhibit divergence by forming __________ with several other neurons.</display>
      <response>synapses</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Therefore, a __________ of a neuronal pool may exhibit divergence by forming synapses with several other neurons.</display>
      <response>neuron</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Therefore, a neuron of a neuronal pool may exhibit divergence by forming synapses with __________.</display>
      <response>several other neurons</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>As a result of divergence, an impulse originating from a single motor neuron in the __________ may stimulate several muscle fibers in a skeletal muscle to contract.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
    </cluster>
    <cluster>
      <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Similarly, an impulse originating from a sensory receptor may diverge and reach several different regions of the __________, where the information can be processed and evoke a response.</display>
      <response>CNS</response>
      <parameter>0,.71</parameter>
      <display>Similarly, an impulse originating from a __________ may diverge and reach several different regions of the CNS, where the information can be processed and evoke a response.</display>
      <response>sensory receptor</response>
    </cluster>
  </clusters>
</setspec>
