<setspec>
    <clusters>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7316999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable that is allowed to vary and is observed in relation to the IV (dependent on the independent variable)</display>
            <response>dependent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7315999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable that receives stimulus and measured for the effect the treatment has had upon it.</display>
            <response>dependent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7314999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a variable that varies due, at least in part, to the impact of the independent variable. In other words, its value 'depends' on the value of the independent variable. For example, in the variables 'gender' and 'academic major,' academic major is the __________, meaning that your major cannot determine whether you are male or female, but your gender might indirectly lead you to favor one major over another.</display>
            <response>dependent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7313999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The outcome variable. In experimental research, this variable is expected to depend on a predictor (or independent) variable.</display>
            <response>dependent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7312999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The variable that is measured to tell you the outcome.</display>
            <response>dependent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7311999999999999</parameter>
            <display>variable that may change in response to manipulations of the IV (what is measured)</display>
            <response>dependent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7310999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The variable that is controlled by an experimenter</display>
            <response>independent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7309999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable that is part of the situation that exist from which originates the stimulus given to a dependent variable. Includes treatment, state of variable, such as age, size, weight, etc.</display>
            <response>independent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7308999999999999</parameter>
            <display>experimental factor that is manipulated; variable whose effect is being studied.</display>
            <response>independent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7307999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the conditions of an experiment that are systematically manipulated by the researcher. A variable that is not impacted by the dependent variable, and that itself impacts the dependent variable.</display>
            <response>independent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7306999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The variable that the experimenter manipulates (changes).</display>
            <response>independent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7305999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The variables that the researcher expects to be the cause of an outcome of interest. For example, if a researcher wants to examine the effect of gender on income, gender is the __________. Sometimes this variable is referred to as the treatment variable or the causal variable.</display>
            <response>independent variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7304999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An intensive investigation of the current and past behaviors and experiences of a single person, family, group, or organization.</display>
            <response>case study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7303999999999999</parameter>
            <display>descriptive research technique in which one person or a small group is studied in depth in hope of revealing universal principles</display>
            <response>case study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7302999999999999</parameter>
            <display>In-depth investigation of a single person, group or event, where data are gathered from a variety of sources and by using several different methods (e.g. observations and interviews).</display>
            <response>case study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7301999999999999</parameter>
            <display>in-depth, intensive investigation of individual or small group of people which involves interviews and personal interpretations by researcher. It may also be supplemented with psychological or medical tests</display>
            <response>case study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7300999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the collection and presentation of detailed information about a particular participant or small group, frequently including data derived from the subjects themselves.</display>
            <response>case study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7299999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable in which both order of data points and distance between data points can be determined, e.g., percentage scores and distances</display>
            <response>interval variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7298999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable wherein the distance between units is the same but the zero point is arbitrary.</display>
            <response>interval variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7297999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Data measured in fixed units with equal distance between points on the scale</display>
            <response>interval variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7296999999999999</parameter>
            <display>differences between values can be found, but is NO absolute ZERO. Examples: temperature F, time</display>
            <response>interval variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7295999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a form of categorical data, using 'names'.</display>
            <response>nominal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7294999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable determined by categories which cannot be ordered, e.g., gender and color</display>
            <response>nominal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7293999999999999</parameter>
            <display>data of categories only. Data cannot be arranged in an ordering scheme. (Gender, Race, Religion)</display>
            <response>nominal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7292999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Frequency count data that consists of the number of participants falling into categories. (e.g. 7 people passed their driving test first time, 6 didn’t).</display>
            <response>nominal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7291999999999999</parameter>
            <display>This type of distribution is seen when the variables are clustered together with gradual decrease on either side of the distribution</display>
            <response>normal distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7290999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A normal frequency distribution representing the probability that a majority of randomly selected members of a population will fall within the middle of the distribution. Represented by the bell curve.</display>
            <response>normal distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7289999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An arrangement of a data that is symmetrical and forms a bell shaped pattern where the mean, median and mode all fall in the centre at the highest peak</display>
            <response>normal distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7288999999999999</parameter>
            <display>bell-shaped curve that results when values of a trait in a population are plotted against their frequency</display>
            <response>normal distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7287999999999999</parameter>
            <display>This distribution describes a frequency distribution of data points that resembles a bell shape.</display>
            <response>normal distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7286999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable in which the order of data points can be determined but not the distance between data points, e.g., letter grades</display>
            <response>ordinal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7285999999999999</parameter>
            <display>data exists in categories that are ordered but differences cannot be determined or they are meaningless. (Example: 1st, 2nd, 3rd)</display>
            <response>ordinal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7284999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Data that is capable of being out into rank order (e.g. places in a beauty contest, or ratings for attractiveness).</display>
            <response>ordinal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7283999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Data that is discrete categories, but that can also be ranked. For example, if a survey ask individuals whether they 'strongly agree', 'agree', 'disagree', or 'strongly disagree' with a statement, the responses would be ordinal because they are in categories, but they can also be ranked.</display>
            <response>ordinal variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7282999999999999</parameter>
            <display>ALL of the individual you wish to study (ex. all students in the US)</display>
            <response>population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7281999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A clearly defined group of people or objects. Samples are drawn from the __________ and statistical results that are derived from random samples can be generalized to the whole __________.</display>
            <response>population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7280999999999999</parameter>
            <display>all cases in a group, from which samples may be drawn for a study</display>
            <response>population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7279999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The target group under investigation, as in all students enrolled in first-year composition courses taught in traditional classrooms. The __________ is the entire set under consideration. Samples are drawn from __________s.</display>
            <response>population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7278999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the target group under investigation. The __________ is the entire set under consideration. Samples are drawn from __________s.</display>
            <response>population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7277999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a research method that looks like an experiment BUT subjects are not randomly assigned to control and experimental groups (no cause and effect can be drawn)</display>
            <response>quasi-experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7276999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An experiment often conducted in controlled conditions where the IV simply exists so there can be no random allocation to the conditions</display>
            <response>quasi-experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7275999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Research in which individuals cannot be assigned randomly to two groups, but some environmental factor influences who belongs to each group. For example, if researchers want to look at the effects of smoking on health, they cannot ethically assign individuals to a group that smokes and a group that does not smoke.</display>
            <response>quasi-experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7274999999999999</parameter>
            <display>researchers takes subjects and conditions as they naturally occur, with little if any control over what happens.</display>
            <response>quasi-experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7273999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Similar to true experiments. Have subjects, treatment, etc., but uses nonrandomized groups. Incorporates interpretation and transferability in order to compensate for lack of control of variables.</display>
            <response>quasi-experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7272999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A measure of dispersion of data. The __________ is calculated by subtracting the value of the lowest data point from the value of the highest data point.</display>
            <response>range</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7271999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A measure of dispersion which involves subtracting the lowest score from the highest score in a set of data</display>
            <response>range</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7270999999999999</parameter>
            <display>difference between highest and lowest scores in a distribution.</display>
            <response>range</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7269999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The difference between the highest and lowest scores in adistribution.</display>
            <response>range</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7268999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The distance between the lowest and the highest value in a set of scores.</display>
            <response>range</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7267999999999999</parameter>
            <display>extent to which a test yields consistent results - a measure is repeatable</display>
            <response>reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7266999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The consistency and dependability of a survey question or set of questions to gather data. Reliability indicates the degree to which survey questions will provide the same result over time for the same person, across similar groups, and irrespective of who collects the survey data. A reliable set of questions will always give the same result on different occasions, assuming that what is being measured has not changed during the intervening period.</display>
            <response>reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7265999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the degree to which a measure yields consistent results. If the measuring instrument [e.g., survey] is reliable, then administering it to similar groups would yield similar results. Reliability is a prerequisite for validity. An unreliable indicator cannot produce trustworthy results.</display>
            <response>reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7264999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which a measure, procedure or instrument yields the same result on repeated trials.</display>
            <response>reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7263999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Whether something is consistent. In the case of a study, whether it is replicable.</display>
            <response>reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7262999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A measure of the average spread of scores around the mean. The greater the __________ the more spread out the scores are. .</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7261999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A measure of variability or dispersion of a set of data. The __________ (SD) is the square root of the variance. It is calculated based on the difference between each individual observation and the mean observation.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7260999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a measure of variation that indicates the typical distance between the scores of a distribution and the mean; it is determined by taking the square root of the average of the squared deviations in a given distribution. It can be used to indicate the proportion of data within certain ranges of scale values when the distribution conforms closely to the normal curve.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7259999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A term used in statistical analysis. A measure of variation that indicates the typical distance between the scores of adistribution and the mean; it is determined by taking the square root of the average of the squared deviations in a given distribution.It can be used to indicate the proportion of data within certain ranges of scale values when the distribution conforms closely to the normal curve.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7258999999999999</parameter>
            <display>computed measure of how much scores vary around the mean score.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7257999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A group in an experiment that receives not treatment in order to compare the treated group against a norm.</display>
            <response>control group</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7256999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A group that is treated normally and gives us a measure of how people behave when they are not exposed to the experimental treatment (e.g. allowed to sleep normally).</display>
            <response>control group</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7255999999999999</parameter>
            <display>In an experiment, the __________ does not receive the intervention or treatment under investigation. This group may also be referred to as the comparison group.</display>
            <response>control group</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7254999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the group in an experimental design that receives either no treatment or a different treatment from the experimental group. This group can thus be compared to the experimental group.</display>
            <response>control group</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7253999999999999</parameter>
            <display>measurements or observations (aka scores)</display>
            <response>data</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7252999999999999</parameter>
            <display>factual information [as measurements or statistics] used as a basis for reasoning, discussion, or calculation.</display>
            <response>data</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7251999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Information collected through surveys, interviews, or observations. Statistics are produced from __________, and __________ must be processed to be of practical use.</display>
            <response>data</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7250999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Recorded observations, usually in numeric or textual form</display>
            <response>data</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7249999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Individuals in this type of experimentation do receive the treatment being tested</display>
            <response>experimental condition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7248999999999999</parameter>
            <display>condition of experiment that exposes participants to treatment, that is, to one version of the IV</display>
            <response>experimental condition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7247999999999999</parameter>
            <display>In experimental research, the group of subjects who receive the experimental treatment or intervention under investigation.</display>
            <response>experimental condition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7246999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The group that received the experimental treatment (e.g. sleep deprivation)</display>
            <response>experimental condition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7245999999999999</parameter>
            <display>How a measure or procedure appears.</display>
            <response>face validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7244999999999999</parameter>
            <display>measures whether a test looks like it tests what it is supposed to test as determined by a quick look or evaluation by a non expert</display>
            <response>face validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7243999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Simple way of assessing whether a test measures what it claims to measure which is concerned with face value – e.g. does an IQ test look like it tests intelligence.</display>
            <response>face validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7242999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which a survey or a test appears to actually measure what the researcher claims it measures. For example, a researcher may create survey questions that s/he claims measure gender role attitudes. To have __________, other researchers who read the survey questions must also agree that the questions do appear to measure gender role attitudes.</display>
            <response>face validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7241999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A statement that predicts the relationship between the independent (causal) and dependent (outcome) variables.</display>
            <response>hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7240999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a tentative explanation based on theory to predict a causal relationship between variables.</display>
            <response>hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7239999999999999</parameter>
            <display>testable prediction, often implied by a theory</display>
            <response>hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7238999999999999</parameter>
            <display>This is a formal statement or prediction of what the researcher expects to find. It needs to be testable.</display>
            <response>hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7237999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A measure of the consistency between the ratings or values assigned to a behavior that is being rated or observed; usually expressed as a percentage of agreement between two raters/observers, or as a coefficient of agreement which can be stated as a probability.</display>
            <response>inter-rater reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7236999999999999</parameter>
            <display>More than one individual scores same test, regardless of who rates test - scores should be the same for _____ reliability</display>
            <response>inter-rater reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7235999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which two or more individuals agree. It addresses the consistency of the implementation of a rating system.</display>
            <response>inter-rater reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7234999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which two or more observers are observing and recording behaviour in the same way</display>
            <response>inter-rater reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7233999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A descriptive statistic used as a measure of central tendency. To calculate the __________, all the values of a variable are added and then the sum is divided by the number of values. For example, if the age of the respondents in a sample were 21, 35, 40, 46, and 76, the __________ age of the sample would be (21+35+40+46+76)/5 = 43.6</display>
            <response>mean</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7232999999999999</parameter>
            <display>arithmetic average of a distribution,</display>
            <response>mean</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7231999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Measure of central tendency calculated by adding all the scores in a set of data together and dividing by the total number of scores</display>
            <response>mean</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7230999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The average score within a distribution.</display>
            <response>mean</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7229999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A descriptive statistic used to measure central tendency. The __________ is the value that is the middle value of a set of values. 50% of the values lie above the __________, and 50% lie below the __________. For example, if a sample of individuals are ages 21, 34, 46, 55, and 76 the __________ age is 46.</display>
            <response>median</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7228999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Measure of central tendency calculated by arranging scores in a set of data from lowest to highest and finding the middle score</display>
            <response>median</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7227999999999999</parameter>
            <display>middle score in a distribution; half scores are above it and half are below it.</display>
            <response>median</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7226999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The center score in a distribution.</display>
            <response>median</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7225999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A statistical technique that combines and analyzes data across multiple studies on a topic.</display>
            <response>meta-analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7224999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A technique where rather than conducting new research with participants, the researchers examine the results of several studies that have already been conducted</display>
            <response>meta-analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7223999999999999</parameter>
            <display>an analysis combining the results of several studies that address a set of related hypotheses.</display>
            <response>meta-analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7222999999999999</parameter>
            <display>procedure for statistically combining results of many different research studies</display>
            <response>meta-analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7221999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An observation study conducted in the environment where the behaviour would normally occur</display>
            <response>naturalistic observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7220999999999999</parameter>
            <display>descriptive research that involves observing and recording behavior without trying to manipulate and control the situation.</display>
            <response>naturalistic observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7219999999999999</parameter>
            <display>observation of behaviors and events in natural settings without experimental manipulation or other forms of interference.</display>
            <response>naturalistic observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7218999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Observational research of a group in its natural setting</display>
            <response>naturalistic observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7217999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable in which the difference between the values on the scale are equivalent and the scale has a fixed zero point; values on the scale can be meaningfully measured against each other.</display>
            <response>ratio variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7216999999999999</parameter>
            <display>data with an absolute 0. Ratios are meaningful. (Length, Width, Weight, Distance)</display>
            <response>ratio variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7215999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The quotient of two values.</display>
            <response>ratio variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7214999999999999</parameter>
            <display>ONLY SOME of the individuals/objects you wish to study from a population (ex. 1000 students from New York)</display>
            <response>sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7213999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A group of people that are drawn from the target population to take part in a research investigation</display>
            <response>sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7212999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A group that is selected from a larger group (the population). By studying the __________ the researcher tries to draw valid conclusions about the population.</display>
            <response>sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7211999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The population researched in a particular study. Usually, attempts are made to select a 'sample population' that is considered representative of groups of people to whom results will be generalized or transferred.</display>
            <response>sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7210999999999999</parameter>
            <display>extent to which a test measures or predicts what it is supposed to - test accuracy</display>
            <response>validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7209999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The degree to which a study accurately reflects or assesses the specific concept that the researcher is attempting to measure. A method can be reliable, consistently measuring the same thing, but not valid. See also internal __________ and external __________</display>
            <response>validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7208999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The degree to which data and results are accurate reflections of reality. Validity refers to the concepts that are investigated, the people or objects that are studied; the methods by which data are collected; and the findings that are produced.</display>
            <response>validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7207999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Whether something is true – measures what it sets out to measure.</display>
            <response>validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7206999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A characteristic or condition which has different values for different individuals (ex. height, test scores, gender)</display>
            <response>variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7205999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An attribute or characteristics of a person or an object that varies within the population under investigation (e.g. age, weight, IQ, child care type).</display>
            <response>variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7204999999999999</parameter>
            <display>any characteristic or trait that can vary from one person to another [race, gender, academic major] or for one person over time [age, political beliefs].</display>
            <response>variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7203999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Observable characteristics that vary among individuals. See also ordinal __________, nominal __________, interval __________, continuous __________, discrete __________,dependent __________, independent __________.</display>
            <response>variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7202999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A method of statistical analysis broadly applicable to a number of research designs, used to determine differences among the means of two or more groups on a variable. The independent variables are usually nominal, and the dependent variable is usual an interval.</display>
            <response>anova</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7201999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A statistical test that determines whether the means of two or more groups are significantly different.</display>
            <response>anova</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7200999999999999</parameter>
            <display>statistical method for making simultaneous comparisons between two or more means</display>
            <response>anova</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7199999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A measure that describes the 'typical' or average characteristic; the three main measures of __________ are mean, median and mode.</display>
            <response>central tendency</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7198999999999999</parameter>
            <display>any way of describing or characterizing typical, average, or common values in some distribution.</display>
            <response>central tendency</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7197999999999999</parameter>
            <display>These measures indicate the middle or center of a distribution, and include the median and mode.</display>
            <response>central tendency</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7196999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a research condition in which no one except the researcher(s) knows the identities of the participants in a study. It refers to the treatment of information that a participant has disclosed to the researcher in a relationship of trust and with the expectation that it will not be revealed to others in ways that violate the original consent agreement, unless permission is granted by the participant.</display>
            <response>confidentiality</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7195999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The protection of research subjects from being identified. A common standard in social science research is that records or information used for research should not allow participants to be identified and that researchers should not take any action that would affect the individual to whom the information pertains.</display>
            <response>confidentiality</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7194999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Unless agreed beforehand, participants have the right to expect that all data collected during a research study will remain confidential and anonymous.</display>
            <response>confidentiality</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7193999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable that is not of interest, but which distorts the results if the researcher does not control for it in the analysis. For example, if a researcher is interested in the effect of education on political views, the researcher must control for income. Income is a __________ because it affects political views and education is related to income.</display>
            <response>confounding variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7192999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An extraneous variable that varies systematically with the IV so we cannot be sure of the true source of the change to the DV</display>
            <response>confounding variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7191999999999999</parameter>
            <display>An unforeseen, and unaccounted-for variable that jeopardizes reliability and validity of an experiment's outcome.</display>
            <response>confounding variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7190999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Extent to which scores suggest that a test is actually measuring an ABSTRACT theoretical idea (such as anxiety, personality, introversion, etc.).</display>
            <response>construct validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7189999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Seeks an agreement between a theoretical concept and a specific measuring device, such as observation.</display>
            <response>construct validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7188999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The degree to which a variable, test, questionnaire or instrument measures the theoretical concept that the researcher hopes to measure. For example, if a researcher is interested in the theoretical concept of 'marital satisfaction,' and the researcher uses a questionnaire to measure marital satisfaction, if the questionnaire has __________ it is considered to be a good measure of marital satisfaction.</display>
            <response>construct validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7187999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A procedure for organizing narrative, qualitative data into themes and concepts.</display>
            <response>content analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7186999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Technique used to analyse qualitative data which involves coding the written data into categories – converting qualitative data into quantitative data.</display>
            <response>content analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7185999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the systematic, objective, and quantitative description of the manifest or latent content of print or nonprint communications.</display>
            <response>content analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7184999999999999</parameter>
            <display>degree to which test is representative of total domain its supposed to cover.</display>
            <response>content validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7183999999999999</parameter>
            <display>Similar to face validity except that the researcher deliberately targets individuals acknowledged to be experts in the topic area to give their opinions on the validity of the measure.</display>
            <response>content validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7182999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which a measurement reflects the specific intended domain of content.</display>
            <response>content validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7181999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a common statistical analysis, usually abbreviated as r, that measures the degree of relationship between pairs of interval variables in a sample. The range of __________ is from -1.00 to zero to +1.00. Also, a non-cause and effect relationship between two variables.</display>
            <response>correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7180999999999999</parameter>
            <display>measure of the extent to which two factors vary together which can be positive or negative or non</display>
            <response>correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7179999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The degree to which two variables are associated. Variables are positively correlated if they both tend to increase at the same time. Variables are negatively correlated if as one increases the other decreases.</display>
            <response>correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7178999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable that can assume only a finite number of values; it consists of separate, indivisible categories. The opposite of discrete is continuous. For example, one's gender is either 'male' or 'female', thus gender is discrete. A person's height could be 5 feet 1 inch, 5 feet 1.1 inches, 5 feet 1.11 inches, and so on, thus it is continuous.</display>
            <response>discrete variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7177999999999999</parameter>
            <display>A variable that is measured solely in whole units, e.g., gender and siblings</display>
            <response>discrete variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7176999999999999</parameter>
            <display>a variable that is measured solely in whole units, such as, gender and number of siblings.</display>
            <response>discrete variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7175999999999999</parameter>
            <display>The degree to which the results of a study can be generalized beyond the study sample to a larger population.</display>
            <response>external validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7174999999999999</parameter>
            <display>the extent to which the results of a study are generalizable or transferable.</display>
            <response>external validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7174</parameter>
            <display>Whether it is possible to generalise the results beyond the experimental setting.</display>
            <response>external validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7173</parameter>
            <display>A variable that interferes with the relationship between the independent and dependent variables and which therefore needs to be controlled for in some way.</display>
            <response>extraneous variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7172</parameter>
            <display>any variables other than IV variable that seem likely to influence the DV</display>
            <response>extraneous variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7171</parameter>
            <display>Variables that if not controlled may affect the DV and provide a false impression than an IV has produced changes when it hasn’t.</display>
            <response>extraneous variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.717</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which conclusions from analysis of data from a sample can be applied to the population as a whole.</display>
            <response>generalizability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7169</parameter>
            <display>the extent to which research findings and conclusions conducted on a specific study to groups or situations can be applied to the population at large.</display>
            <response>generalizability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7168</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which research findings and conclusions from a study conducted on a sample population can be applied to the population at large.</display>
            <response>generalizability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7167</parameter>
            <display>In relation to experiments, whether the results were due to the manipulation of the IV rather than other factors such as extraneous variables or demand characteristics.</display>
            <response>internal validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7166</parameter>
            <display>The extent to which researchers provide compelling evidence that the causal (independent) variable causes changes in the outcome (dependent) variable. To do this, researchers must rule other potential explanations for the changes in the outcome variable.</display>
            <response>internal validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7165</parameter>
            <display>the rigor with which the study was conducted [e.g., the study's design, the care taken to conduct measurements, and decisions concerning what was and was not measured]. It is also the extent to which the designers of a study have taken into account alternative explanations for any causal relationships they explore. In studies that do not explore causal relationships, only the first of these definitions should be considered when assessing __________.</display>
            <response>internal validity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7164</parameter>
            <display>a theory or analysis of how research does and should proceed.</display>
            <response>methodology</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7163</parameter>
            <display>systematic approaches to the conduct of an operation or process. It includes steps of procedure, application of techniques, systems of reasoning or analysis, and the modes of inquiry employed by a discipline.</display>
            <response>methodology</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7162</parameter>
            <display>The principles, procedures, and strategies of research used in a study for gathering information, analyzing data, and drawing conclusions. There are broad categories of __________ such as qualitative methods or quantitative methods; and there are particular types of methodologies such as survey research, case study, and participant observation, among many others.</display>
            <response>methodology</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7161</parameter>
            <display>A descriptive statistic that is a measure of central tendency. It is the value that occurs most frequently in the data. For example, if survey respondents are ages 21, 33, 33, 45, and 76, the modal age is 33.</display>
            <response>mode</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.716</parameter>
            <display>Measure of central tendency which is the most frequently occurring score in a set of data</display>
            <response>mode</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7159</parameter>
            <display>The most frequent score in a distribution.</display>
            <response>mode</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7158</parameter>
            <display>hypothesis that states there is no difference between two or more sets of data making it opposite of the research hypothesis</display>
            <response>null hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7157</parameter>
            <display>the proposition, to be tested statistically, that the experimental intervention has 'no effect,' meaning that the treatment and control groups will not differ as a result of the intervention. Investigators usually hope that the data will demonstrate some effect from the intervention, thus allowing the investigator to reject the __________.</display>
            <response>null hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7156</parameter>
            <display>This hypothesis states that there is no difference between groups. The alternative hypothesis states that there is some real difference between two or more groups.</display>
            <response>null hypothesis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7155</parameter>
            <display>A value used to describe a population</display>
            <response>parameter</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7154</parameter>
            <display>A characteristic of a population.</display>
            <response>parameter</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7153</parameter>
            <display>A coefficient or value for the population that corresponds to a particular statistic from a sample and is often inferred from the sample.</display>
            <response>parameter</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7152</parameter>
            <display>A field research method whereby the researcher develops knowledge of the composition of a particular setting or society by taking part in the everyday routines and rituals alongside its members. A principle goal of __________ is develop an understanding of a setting from a member's perspective, which may be accomplished through both informal observations and conversations as well as in-depth interviews.</display>
            <response>participant observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7151</parameter>
            <display>Observation study where the researcher actually joins the group or takes part in the situation they are observing.</display>
            <response>participant observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.715</parameter>
            <display>The investigator takes part in the group activity that the researcher plans to study. The researcher also reveals to the group that s/he is studying the group's activities.</display>
            <response>participant observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7149</parameter>
            <display>A description of the likely occurrence of a particular event. Probability is conventionally expressed on a scale from 0 to 1; a rare event has a __________ close to 0, a very common event has a __________ close to 1.</display>
            <response>probability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7148</parameter>
            <display>How likely something is to happen – can be expressed as a number (0.5) or a percentage (50% change of tossing coin and getting a head)</display>
            <response>probability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7147</parameter>
            <display>The chance that a phenomenon has a of occurring randomly. As a statistical measure, it shown as p (the 'p' factor).</display>
            <response>probability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7146</parameter>
            <display>A set of written questions that participants fill in themselves</display>
            <response>questionnaire</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7145</parameter>
            <display>A survey document with questions that are used to gather information from individuals to be used in research.</display>
            <response>questionnaire</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7144</parameter>
            <display>structured sets of questions on specified subjects that are used to gather information, attitudes, or opinions.</display>
            <response>questionnaire</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7143</parameter>
            <display>A sampling technique in which individuals are selected from a population at random. Each individual has a chance of being chosen, and each individual is selected entirely by chance.</display>
            <response>random sampling</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7142</parameter>
            <display>A sampling technique where everyone in the target population has an equal chance of being selected</display>
            <response>random sampling</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7141</parameter>
            <display>Process used in research to draw a sample of a population strictly by chance, yielding no discernible pattern beyond chance. Random sampling can be accomplished by first numbering the population, then selecting the sample according to a table of random numbers or using a random-number computer generator.</display>
            <response>random sampling</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.714</parameter>
            <display>Assigning individuals in a sample to either an experimental group or a control group at random.</display>
            <response>randomization</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7139</parameter>
            <display>Refers to the practice of using chance methods (e.g. flipping a coin' to allocate participants to the conditions of an investigation</display>
            <response>randomization</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7138</parameter>
            <display>Used to allocate subjects to experimental and control groups. The subjects are initially considered not unequal because they were randomly selected.</display>
            <response>randomization</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7137</parameter>
            <display>A discrepancy which occurs between a sample and its population</display>
            <response>sampling error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7136</parameter>
            <display>Fluctuation in the value of a statistic that is calculated from different samples that are drawn from the same population.</display>
            <response>sampling error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7135</parameter>
            <display>the degree to which the results from the sample deviate from those that would be obtained from the entire population, because of random error in the selection of respondent and the corresponding reduction in reliability.</display>
            <response>sampling error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7134</parameter>
            <display>Participants’ behaviour is distorted as they modify this in order to be seen in a positive light.</display>
            <response>social desirability bias</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7133</parameter>
            <display>tendency to give socially approved answers to questions about oneself.</display>
            <response>social desirability bias</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7132</parameter>
            <display>The tendency for respondents to give answers that are socially desirable or acceptable, that may not be accurate.</display>
            <response>social desirability bias</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7131</parameter>
            <display>If there is a very small probability that a relationship observed in statistical analyses is due to chance, the results are said to reach __________. This means that the researcher concludes that there is a real relationship between the observed variables or a real difference between two groups. See Significance Level for additional information.</display>
            <response>statistical significance</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.713</parameter>
            <display>statistical statement of how likely it is that an obtained result occurred by chance - expressed as p or sig.</display>
            <response>statistical significance</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7129</parameter>
            <display>the probability that the difference between the outcomes of the control and experimental group are great enough that it is unlikely due solely to chance. The probability that the null hypothesis can be rejected at a predetermined significance level [0.05 or 0.01].</display>
            <response>statistical significance</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7128</parameter>
            <display>if you take the same test 2x's and you get the same results it shows ______ reliability</display>
            <response>test-retest reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7127</parameter>
            <display>Involves presenting the same participants with the same test or questionnaire on two separate occasions and seeing whether there is a positive correlation between the two</display>
            <response>test-retest reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7126</parameter>
            <display>The degree to which a measure produces consistent results over several administrations.</display>
            <response>test-retest reliability</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7125</parameter>
            <display>a general explanation about a specific behavior or set of events that is based on known principles and serves to organize related events in a meaningful way. A __________ is not as specific as a hypothesis.</display>
            <response>theory</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7124</parameter>
            <display>General statement that describes a hypothesized relationship between different phenomena or characteristics. Theories should be specific enough to be testable with a well-designed research study.</display>
            <response>theory</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7123</parameter>
            <display>set of assumptions used to explain phenomena and offered for scientific study</display>
            <response>theory</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7122</parameter>
            <display>a multi-method or pluralistic approach, using different methods in order to focus on the research topic from different viewpoints and to produce a multi-faceted set of data. Also used to check the validity of findings from any one method.</display>
            <response>triangulation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7121</parameter>
            <display>The use of a combination of research methods in a study. An example of __________ would be a study that incorporated surveys, interviews, and observations. See also multi-modal methods</display>
            <response>triangulation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.712</parameter>
            <display>Using of a variety of research methods to gain a diverse source of data pertaining to a specific research problem or question. This process helps to enhance the validity of data since it does not overly rely on any particular method.</display>
            <response>triangulation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7119</parameter>
            <display>An error that occurs when a researcher concludes that a statistically significant relationship between two variables exists (based on the analysis of the sample), when in fact it the relationship does not exist in the population from which the sample was selected. The probability of making a type I error is decided at the outset of the statistical analysis. This probability is also called a significance level.</display>
            <response>type i error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7118</parameter>
            <display>Error of rejecting null hypothesis when in fact it is true (also called a 'false positive'). You think you found a cause effect relationship but ONE IS NOT THERE</display>
            <response>type i error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7117</parameter>
            <display>Is a false positive. It is where you accept the alternative/experimental hypothesis when it is false</display>
            <response>type i error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7116</parameter>
            <display>An error that occurs when a researcher concludes that no significant relationship between two variables (based on analysis of sample data) when in fact the relationship does exist in the population from which the sample was drawn. The probability of not making a type II error is also called the power of a statistical test.</display>
            <response>type ii error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7115</parameter>
            <display>error of failing to reject a null hypothesis when in fact it is false (also called a 'false negative'). You think there is NO CAUSE EFFECT but THERE IS</display>
            <response>type ii error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7114</parameter>
            <display>Is a false negative. It is where you accept the null hypothesis when it is false</display>
            <response>type ii error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7113</parameter>
            <display>a research condition in which no one, including the researcher, knows the identities of research participants.</display>
            <response>anonymity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7112</parameter>
            <display>An ethical safeguard against invasion of privacy whereby the researcher is unable to identify the respondents by their responses.</display>
            <response>anonymity</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7111</parameter>
            <display>a loss of balance and accuracy in the use of research methods. It can appear in research via the sampling frame, random sampling, or non-response. It can also occur at other stages in research, such as while interviewing, in the design of questions, or in the way data are analyzed and presented. Bias means that the research findings will not be representative of, or generalizable to, a wider population.</display>
            <response>bias</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.711</parameter>
            <display>Influences that distort the results of a research study.</display>
            <response>bias</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7109</parameter>
            <display>a method of statistical analysis where data that share a common trait are grouped together. The data is collected in a way that allows the data collector to group data according to certain characteristics.</display>
            <response>cluster analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7108</parameter>
            <display>A type of multivariate analysis where the collected data are classified based on several characteristics in order to determine groups (or clusters) of cases that would be useful to explore further. This type of analysis can help one determine which groups of variables best predict an outcome.</display>
            <response>cluster analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7107</parameter>
            <display>A range of estimated values that is the best guess as to the true population's value. Confidence intervals are usually calculated for the sample mean. In behavioral research, the acceptable level of confidence is usually 95%.</display>
            <response>confidence interval</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7106</parameter>
            <display>The range around a numeric statistical value obtained from a sample, within which the actual, corresponding value for the population is likely to fall, at a given level of probability.</display>
            <response>confidence interval</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7105</parameter>
            <display>The percentage of times that a confidence interval will include the true population value. If the __________ is .95 this means that if a researcher were to randomly sample a population 100 times, 95% of the time the estimated confidence interval for a value will contain the population's true value. In other words, the researcher can be 95% confident that the confidence interval contains the true population value.</display>
            <response>confidence level</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7104</parameter>
            <display>The specific probability of obtaining some result from a sample if it did not exist in the population as a whole, at or below which the relationship will be regarded as statistically significant.</display>
            <response>confidence level</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7103</parameter>
            <display>A concept. A theoretical creation that cannot be directly observed.</display>
            <response>construct</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7102</parameter>
            <display>refers to any of the following: something that exists theoretically but is not directly observable; a concept developed [constructed] for describing relations among phenomena or for other research purposes; or, a theoretical definition in which concepts are defined in terms of other concepts. For example, intelligence cannot be directly observed or measured; it is a __________.</display>
            <response>construct</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7101</parameter>
            <display>A variable that may have fractional values, e.g., height, weight and time.</display>
            <response>continuous variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.71</parameter>
            <display>A variable that, in theory, can take on any value within a range. The opposite of continuous is discrete. For example, a person's height could be 5 feet 1 inch, 5 feet 1.1 inches, 5 feet 1.11 inches, and so one, thus it is continuous. One's gender is either 'male' or 'female', thus it is discrete.</display>
            <response>continuous variable</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7099</parameter>
            <display>Individuals in this type of experimentation are given no experimental treatment or are given a type of placebo (This condition is used to have a base of reference for the experimental group)</display>
            <response>control condition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7098</parameter>
            <display>condition of experiment that contrasts with experimental condition and serves as a comparison for evaluating the effect of the treatment.</display>
            <response>control condition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7097</parameter>
            <display>A form of scientific investigation in which one variable, termed the independent variable, is manipulated to reveal the effect on another variable, termed the dependent or responding variable, while all other variables in the system are held fixed.</display>
            <response>controlled experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7096</parameter>
            <display>an experimental design with two or more randomly selected groups [an experimental group and control group] in which the researcher controls or introduces the independent variable and measures the dependent variable at least two times [pre- and post-test measurements].</display>
            <response>controlled experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7095</parameter>
            <display>A measure of the degree to which two variables are related. A __________ in always between -1 and +1. If the __________ is between 0 and +1 then the variables are positively correlated. If the __________ is between 0 and -1 then the variables are negatively correlated.</display>
            <response>correlation coefficient</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7094</parameter>
            <display>statistical measure of strength of association between two variables ranging from -1.0 to 1.0</display>
            <response>correlation coefficient</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7093</parameter>
            <display>a product of the correlation of two related variables times their standard deviations. Used in true experiments to measure the difference of treatment between them.</display>
            <response>covariate</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7092</parameter>
            <display>A product of the correlation of two related variables times their standard deviations. Used in true experiments to measure the difference of treatment between them.</display>
            <response>covariate</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7091</parameter>
            <display>After completing the research, the true aim is revealed to the participant. Aim of __________ = to return the person to the state s/he was in before they took part.</display>
            <response>debriefing</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.709</parameter>
            <display>giving participants in a research study a complete explanation of the study after the study is completed needed for deception</display>
            <response>debriefing</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7089</parameter>
            <display>Involves misleading participants about the purpose of s study.</display>
            <response>deception</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7088</parameter>
            <display>method by which participants are misinformed or misled about study's methods and purposes - must be told truth about this in debriefing</display>
            <response>deception</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7087</parameter>
            <display>Analysis of data that helps describe, show or summarize data in a meaningful way</display>
            <response>descriptive statistics</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7086</parameter>
            <display>Basic statistics used to describe and summarize data. Descriptive statistics generally include measures of the average values of variables (mean, median, and mode) and measures of the dispersion of variables (variance, standard deviation, or range).</display>
            <response>descriptive statistics</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7085</parameter>
            <display>The frequency with which values of a variable occur in a sample or a population. To graph a __________, first the values of the variables are listed across the bottom of the graph. The number of times the value occurs are listed up the side of the graph. A bar is drawn that corresponds to how many times each value occurred in the data.</display>
            <response>distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7084</parameter>
            <display>the range of values of a particular variable.</display>
            <response>distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70830000000000001</parameter>
            <display>A research design where both the experimenter and the subjects are unaware of which is the treatment group and which is the control.</display>
            <response>double-blind experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70820000000000001</parameter>
            <display>experimental procedure in which both research participants and research staff are ignorant about whether the research participants have received the treatment or a placebo.</display>
            <response>double-blind experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70810000000000001</parameter>
            <display>A measure of the strength of the effect of the predictor (or independent) variable on the outcome (or dependent) variable.</display>
            <response>effect size</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70800000000000001</parameter>
            <display>the amount of change in a dependent variable that can be attributed to manipulations of the independent variable. A large __________ exists when the value of the dependent variable is strongly influenced by the independent variable. It is the mean difference on a variable between experimental and control groups divided by the standard deviation on that variable of the pooled groups or of the control group alone.</display>
            <response>effect size</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70790000000000001</parameter>
            <display>'…the process of developing systematized knowledge gained from observations that are formulated to support insights and generalizations about the phenomena under study'.</display>
            <response>empirical research</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70780000000000001</parameter>
            <display>the process of developing systematized knowledge gained from observations that are formulated to support insights and generalizations about the phenomena being researched.</display>
            <response>empirical research</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70770000000000001</parameter>
            <display>A way of understanding and explaining how we know what we know. Each research methodology is underpinned by an __________ that serves as a guiding philosophy and provides a concrete process of research steps.</display>
            <response>epistemology</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70760000000000001</parameter>
            <display>concerns knowledge construction; asks what constitutes knowledge and how knowledge is validated.</display>
            <response>epistemology</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70750000000000001</parameter>
            <display>Ethnographies study groups and/or cultures over a period of time. The goal of this type of research is to comprehend the particular group/culture through observer immersion into the culture or group. Research is completed through various methods, which are similar to those of case studies, but since the researcher is immersed within the group for an extended period of time more detailed information is usually collected during the research.</display>
            <response>ethnography</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70740000000000001</parameter>
            <display>Literally meaning 'folk' or 'people' 'writing,' __________ is a field method focused on recording the details of social life occurring in a society. A primary objective is to gain a rich, 'thick' understanding of a setting and of the members within a society. Ethnographers seek to learn the language, thoughts, and practices of a society by participating in the rituals and observing the everyday routines of the community. Ethnography is primarily based upon participant observation, direct observation, and in-depth interviewing</display>
            <response>ethnography</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70730000000000001</parameter>
            <display>A researcher working within this methodology creates an environment in which to observe and interpret the results of a research question. A key element in __________al research is that participants in a study are randomly assigned to groups. In an attempt to create a causal model (i.e., to discover the causal origin of a particular phenomenon), groups are treated differently and measurements are conducted to determine if different treatments appear to lead to different effects.</display>
            <response>experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70720000000000001</parameter>
            <display>research method in which investigator manipulates one or more factors (IV) to observe effect on some behavior or mental process (DV)</display>
            <response>experiment</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70710000000000001</parameter>
            <display>A statistical test that explores relationships among data. The test explores which variables in a data set are most related to each other. In a carefully constructed survey, for example, __________ can yield information on patterns of responses, not simply data on a single response. Larger tendencies may then be interpreted, indicating behavior trends rather than simply responses to specific questions.</display>
            <response>factor analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70700000000000001</parameter>
            <display>An exploratory form of multivariate analysis that takes a large number of variables or objects and aims to identify a small number of factors that explain the interrelations among the variables or objects.</display>
            <response>factor analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.70690000000000001</parameter>
            <display>An interview conducted with a small group of people, all at one time, to explore ideas on a particular topic. The goal of a __________ is to uncover additional information through participants' exchange of ideas.</display>
            <response>focus group</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7068</parameter>
            <display>small, roundtable discussion groups charged with examining specific topics or problems, including possible options or solutions. Focus groups usually consist of 4-12 participants, guided by moderators to keep the discussion flowing and to collect and report the results.</display>
            <response>focus group</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7067</parameter>
            <display>Practice of developing other theories that emerge from observing a group. Theories are grounded in the group's observable experiences, but researchers add their own insight into why those experiences exist.</display>
            <response>grounded theory</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7066</parameter>
            <display>The development of social science theory from the inductive analysis of data. This approach is generally used in qualitative research. The specific and detailed observations in the data are studied and understood to such an extent that a theory of more general patterns of behavior can be generated.</display>
            <response>grounded theory</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7065</parameter>
            <display>A graph that is used for continuous data (e.g. test scores). There should be no space between the bars, because the data is continuous.</display>
            <response>histogram</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7064</parameter>
            <display>A visual presentation of data that shows the frequencies with which each value of a variable occurs. Each value of a variable typically is displayed along the bottom of a __________, and a bar is drawn for each value. The height of the bar corresponds to the frequency with which that value occurs.</display>
            <response>histogram</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7063</parameter>
            <display>perception of a correlation between variables where none exists.</display>
            <response>illusory correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7062</parameter>
            <display>perception of relationship where none exists.</display>
            <response>illusory correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7061</parameter>
            <display>A type of composite measure that summarizes several specific observations and represents a more general dimension.</display>
            <response>index</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.706</parameter>
            <display>A variable that is a summed composite of other variables that are assumed to reflect the same underlying construct.</display>
            <response>index</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7059</parameter>
            <display>Psychologists should ensure that all participants are helped to understand fully all aspects of the research before they agree (give consent) to take part</display>
            <response>informed consent</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7058</parameter>
            <display>The agreement between concerned parties about the data-gathering process and/or the disclosure, reporting, and/or use of data, information, and/or results from a research experiment.</display>
            <response>informed consent</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7057</parameter>
            <display>A relationship exists between two covariables where as one increases, the other decreases</display>
            <response>negative correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7056</parameter>
            <display>association between increases in one variable and decreases in another</display>
            <response>negative correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7055</parameter>
            <display>A source of bias that occurs when non-respondents differ in important ways from respondents.</display>
            <response>nonresponse error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7054</parameter>
            <display>A type of error that is caused when a portion of the sample with particular characteristics do not respond to a survey.</display>
            <response>nonresponse error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7053</parameter>
            <display>statement of procedures used to define research variables which helps to enable replication</display>
            <response>operational definition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7052</parameter>
            <display>statement that describes how to measure a particular variable or define a particular term specifically in a study</display>
            <response>operational definition</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7051</parameter>
            <display>A longitudinal study in which a group of individuals (a panel) is interviewed on several occasions over time.</display>
            <response>panel study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.705</parameter>
            <display>a longitudinal study in which a group of individuals is interviewed at intervals over a period of time.</display>
            <response>panel study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7049</parameter>
            <display>Before going to publication, a research report is sent other psychologists who are knowledgeable in the research topic for them to review the study, and check for any problems</display>
            <response>peer-review</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7048</parameter>
            <display>the process in which the author of a book, article, or other type of publication submits his or her work to experts in the field for critical evaluation, usually prior to publication. This is standard procedure in publishing scholarly research.</display>
            <response>peer-review</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7047</parameter>
            <display>Percentage of scores falling at or below a specific score.</display>
            <response>percentile</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7046</parameter>
            <display>The percent of observations in a sample that have a value below a given score.</display>
            <response>percentile</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7045</parameter>
            <display>A small scale research study that is conducted prior to the larger, final study. The __________ gives researchers a chance to identify any problems with their proposed sampling scheme, methodology, or data collection process. These studies are very useful in accessing strengths and weakness of a potential study.</display>
            <response>pilot study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7044</parameter>
            <display>A small scale study conducted to ensure the method will work according to plan. If it doesn’t then amendments can be made.</display>
            <response>pilot study</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7043</parameter>
            <display>A relationship exists between two covariables where as one increases, so does the other</display>
            <response>positive correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7042</parameter>
            <display>correlation where as one variable increases, the other also increases, or as one decreases so does the other. Both variables move in same direction.</display>
            <response>positive correlation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7041</parameter>
            <display>A field of social research that is carried out in naturalistic settings and generates data largely through observations and interviews. Compared to quantitative research, which is principally concerned with making inferences from randomly selected samples to a larger population, __________ is primarily focused on describing small samples in non-statistical ways.</display>
            <response>qualitative research</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.704</parameter>
            <display>Empirical research in which the researcher explores relationships using textual, rather than quantitative data. Case study, observation, and ethnography are considered forms of __________. Results are not usually considered generalizable, but are often transferable.</display>
            <response>qualitative research</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7039</parameter>
            <display>A technique used to choose subjects at random so as to get a representative sample of the population. In __________, each individual in the eligible population has a fixed and determinate probability of selection into the sample.</display>
            <response>random selection</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7038</parameter>
            <display>procedure that ensures every person in a population has an equal chance of being chosen to participate</display>
            <response>random selection</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7037</parameter>
            <display>A sample that that closely matched the target population as a whole in terms of key variables and characteristics</display>
            <response>representative sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7036</parameter>
            <display>sample in which the participants closely match the characteristics of the population, and thus, all segments of the population are represented in the sample. A __________ allows results to be generalized from the sample to the population.</display>
            <response>representative sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7035</parameter>
            <display>In survey research, the actual percentage of questionnaires completed and returned.</display>
            <response>response rate</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7034</parameter>
            <display>The number of individuals who completed interviews divided by the number individuals who were originally asked or selected to be interviewed.</display>
            <response>response rate</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7033</parameter>
            <display>A list of the entire population eligible to be included within the specific parameters of a research study.</display>
            <response>sampling frame</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7032</parameter>
            <display>A listing that should include all those in the population to be sampled and exclude all those who are not in the population.</display>
            <response>sampling frame</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7031</parameter>
            <display>A method of data collection in which the interviewer uses a pre-determined list of topics or questions to gather information from a respondent. The interviewer, however, may stray from the list to follow-up on things the respondent says during the interview.</display>
            <response>semi-structured interview</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.703</parameter>
            <display>Interview that has some pre-determined questions, but the interviewer can develop others in response to answers given by the participant</display>
            <response>semi-structured interview</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7029</parameter>
            <display>An arrangement of data that is not symmetrical as data is clustered ro one end of the distribution</display>
            <response>skewed distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7028</parameter>
            <display>Any distribution which is lopsided, that is not symmetrical along the x-axis</display>
            <response>skewed distribution</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7027</parameter>
            <display>A value used to describe a sample</display>
            <response>statistic</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7026</parameter>
            <display>A measure of the characteristics of a sample (e.g., the mean is a __________ that measures the average of a sample). It gives an estimate of the same value for the population from which the sample was selected.</display>
            <response>statistic</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7025</parameter>
            <display>application of statistical processes and theory to the compilation, presentation, discussion, and interpretation of numerical data.</display>
            <response>statistical analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7024</parameter>
            <display>The principle of gathering data from a sample of individuals and using those data to make inferences about the wider population from which the sample was drawn.</display>
            <response>statistical analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7023</parameter>
            <display>A sampling technique where groups of participants are selected in proportion to their frequency in the target population</display>
            <response>stratified sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7022</parameter>
            <display>sample drawn in such a way that known subgroups within a population are represented in proportion to their numbers in general population</display>
            <response>stratified sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7021</parameter>
            <display>A statistical method for testing different theorized models, including the 'structures' of relationships among the observed indicators and their underlying concepts.</display>
            <response>stratified sampling</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.702</parameter>
            <display>A type of probability sample where the units in a population of interest are divided into mutually exclusive and collectively exhaustive strata and a (proportionate or disproportionate) random sample is drawn from each stratum.</display>
            <response>stratified sampling</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7019</parameter>
            <display>Interview where the questions are fixed and the interviewer reads them out and records the responses</display>
            <response>structured interview</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7018</parameter>
            <display>The interviewer asks respondents the same questions using a predetermined series of interview questions. Deviations from the predetermined series of questions are not allowed in the interview process.</display>
            <response>structured interview</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7017</parameter>
            <display>A research tool that includes at least one question which is either open-ended or close-ended and employs an oral or written method for asking these questions. The goal of a __________ is to gain specific information about either a specific group or a representative sample of a particular group. Results are typically used to understand the attitudes, beliefs, or knowledge of a particular group.</display>
            <response>survey</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7016</parameter>
            <display>research method in which info is obtained by asking many individuals a fixed set of questions</display>
            <response>survey</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7015</parameter>
            <display>The group that the researchers draws the sample from and wants to be able to generalise the findings to</display>
            <response>target population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7014</parameter>
            <display>The population to which the researcher would like to generalize her or his results based on analysis of a sample. The sample is selected from a __________.</display>
            <response>target population</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7013</parameter>
            <display>A statistical test that is used to compare the means of two samples or the mean of one sample with some fixed value. The test is appropriate for small sample sizes (less than 30) when they are normally distributed.</display>
            <response>t-test</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7012</parameter>
            <display>A statistical test. A __________ is used to determine if the scores of two groups differ on a single variable. For instance, to determine whether writing ability differs among students in two classrooms, a __________ could be used.</display>
            <response>t-test</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7011</parameter>
            <display>the basic observable entity or phenomenon being analyzed by a study and for which data are collected in the form of variables.</display>
            <response>unit of analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.701</parameter>
            <display>The person, group of people, or object that is under study. For example, if an analysis examines children's well-being, children are the __________. If an analysis examines family income, families are the __________.</display>
            <response>unit of analysis</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7009</parameter>
            <display>Also know as a clinical interview, there are no fixed questions just general aims and it is more like a conversation</display>
            <response>unstructured interview</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7008</parameter>
            <display>An interview in which the researcher asks open-ended questions. The researcher aims to give respondents the latitude to talk freely on a topic and to influence the direction of the interview. There is no predetermined plan about the specific information to be gathered from these types of interviews.</display>
            <response>unstructured interview</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7007</parameter>
            <display>A commonly used measure of dispersion for variables. The __________ is calculated by squaring the standard deviation. The __________ is based on the square of the difference between the values for each observation and the mean value.</display>
            <response>variance</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7006</parameter>
            <display>A measure of variation within a distribution, determined by averaging the squared deviations from the mean of a distribution.</display>
            <response>variance</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7005</parameter>
            <display>Scores adjusted by such factors as the importance of the attribute assessed or the reliability and validity of the assessment from which the score was derived, or a combination of such factors.</display>
            <response>weighted scores</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7004</parameter>
            <display>scores in which the components are modified by different multipliers to reflect their relative importance.</display>
            <response>weighted scores</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7003</parameter>
            <display>occur when the questions asked on a sample survey are confusing or leading</display>
            <response>wording effects</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7002</parameter>
            <display>when a specific word used in a question affects how respondents answer the question or the order of the questions</display>
            <response>wording effects</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7001</parameter>
            <display>A score that is produced by subtracting the mean value from an individual data value and dividing by the standard deviation. This standardizes data values and allows for individual data values from different distributions (distributions with different means and standard deviations) to be compared.</display>
            <response>z score</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <parameter>0.7</parameter>
            <display>in a normal distribution it tells you how far a number is above or below mean in terms of standard deviations.</display>
            <response>z score</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>Age?</display>
            <response>18-25</response>
            <falseResponse>26-34</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>35-54</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>55-64</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>65 and over</falseResponse>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>Gender?</display>
            <response>Male</response>
            <falseResponse>Female</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>Other</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>Prefer not to answer</falseResponse>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>Which is the highest level of education you have completed?</display>
            <response>Less than High School</response>
            <falseResponse>High School or GED</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>Some College</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>4-year College Degree/ Bachelors</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>Graduate Degree</falseResponse>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>How many college Research Methods classes have you taken?</display>
            <response>0</response>
            <falseResponse>1</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>2</falseResponse>
            <falseResponse>3 or more</falseResponse>
        </cluster>
    </clusters>
</setspec>