<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<setspec> 
    <clusters>
        <cluster> <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <display>Although __________ are variable they are intended to represent the population from which they come. </display>
            <response>samples~Correct;statistics~Statistics is incorrect. The correct response is samples. Statistics describes the features of a sample which in turn may represent a population.;observations~Observations is incorrect. The correct response is samples. Observations are the behaviors or actions of a sample not a population.;.*~Incorrect. The correct fill-in is 'samples'.</response> 
            <display>Although samples are __________ they are intended to represent the population from which they come. </display>
            <response>variable~Correct;random~Random is incorrect. The correct answer is variable. Random is too strong a word here, since some samples are not always random, but may be biased. Even biased samples are variable, except for the strange case of a degenerate disrtibution.;small~Small is incorrect. The correct answer is variable. While samples in normal situations are smaller than the population, they still may be very very large, restrained by only the size of the population.;.*~Incorrect. The correct fill-in is 'variable'.</response> 
            <display>Although samples are variable they are intended to __________ the population from which they come. </display>
            <response>represent~Correct;describe~;sample~Sample is incorrect. The correct response is represent. The response should describe the relationship between sample and population therefore represent is a proper descriptive word.;.*~Incorrect. The correct fill-in is 'represent'.</response> 
            <display>Although samples are variable they are intended to represent the __________ from which they come. </display>
            <response>population~Correct;sample~Sample is incorrect. The correct response is population. While English allows us to take a sample of a sample, this is not generally done in statistic. Rather in statistics the sample is taken from the population, which we use the sample ot make inferences about.;.*~Incorrect. The correct fill-in is 'population'.</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>When a study __________ human subjects, the sample is the group of people who participated in the study.</display>
            <response>involves</response>
            <display>When a study involves human __________s, the sample is the group of people who participated in the study.</display>
            <response>subject</response>
            <display>When a study involves human subjects, the __________ is the group of people who participated in the study.</display>
            <response>sample</response>
            <display>When a study involves human subjects, the sample is the group of people who __________ in the study.</display>
            <response>participated</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>A __________ describes a characteristic of a sample.</display>
            <response>statistic</response>
            <display>A statistic __________ a characteristic of a sample.</display>
            <response>describes</response>
            <display>A statistic describes a __________ of a sample.</display>
            <response>characteristic</response>
            <display>A statistic describes a characteristic of a __________.</display>
            <response>sample</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________, or average, is a statistic that represents what we expect for observations in the sample.</display>
            <response>sample mean</response>
            <display>The sample mean, or average, is a __________ that represents what we expect for observations in the sample.</display>
            <response>statistic</response>
            <display>The sample mean, or average, is a statistic that __________ what we expect for observations in the sample.</display>
            <response>represents</response>
            <display>The sample mean, or average, is a statistic that represents what we __________ for observations in the sample.</display>
            <response>expect</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ is computed by taking the sum of all the numbers in a set divided by the count of the numbers in the set.</display>
            <response>mean</response>
            <display>The mean is computed by taking the __________ of all the numbers in a set divided by the count of the numbers in the set.</display>
            <response>sum</response>
            <display>The mean is computed by taking the sum of all the numbers in a set __________ by the count of the numbers in the set.</display>
            <response>divided</response>
            <display>The mean is computed by taking the sum of all the numbers in a set divided by the __________ of the numbers in the set.</display>
            <response>count</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>__________ refers to how different the observations are from each other and the mean.</display>
            <response>variability</response>
            <display>Variability refers to how __________ the observations are from each other and the mean.</display>
            <response>different</response>
            <display>Variability refers to how different the __________ are from each other and the mean.</display>
            <response>observations</response>
            <display>Variability refers to how different the observations are from each other and the __________.</display>
            <response>mean</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ for an observation is the squared difference from the mean.</display>
            <response>variance</response>
            <display>The variance for an observation is the __________ difference from the mean.</display>
            <response>squared</response>
            <display>The variance for an observation is the squared __________ from the mean.</display>
            <response>difference</response>
            <display>The variance for an observation is the squared difference from the __________.</display>
            <response>mean</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ for a sample is computed by dividing the sum of the observation __________s by 1 less than the total observations.</display>
            <response>variance</response>
            <display>The variance for a __________ is computed by dividing the sum of the observation variances by 1 less than the total observations.</display>
            <response>sample</response>
            <display>The variance for a sample is computed by __________ the sum of the observation variances by 1 less than the total observations.</display>
            <response>dividing</response>
            <display>The variance for a sample is computed by dividing the sum of the observation variances by __________ less than the total observations.</display>
            <response>1</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ is a statistic that describes typical variability for an observation.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
            <display>The standard deviation is a __________ that describes typical variability for an observation.</display>
            <response>statistic</response>
            <display>The standard deviation is a statistic that describes typical __________ for an observation.</display>
            <response>variability</response>
            <display>The standard deviation is a statistic that describes typical variability for an __________.</display>
            <response>observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>__________ is the square root of the variance, also known as root mean squared error.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
            <display>Standard deviation is the __________ of the variance, also known as root mean squared error.</display>
            <response>square root</response>
            <display>Standard deviation is the square root of the __________, also known as root mean squared error.</display>
            <response>variance</response>
            <display>Standard deviation is the square root of the variance, also known as __________.</display>
            <response>root mean squared error</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ for the standard deviation are the same __________ used to measure the observations.</display>
            <response>units</response>
            <display>The units for the __________ are the same units used to measure the observations.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
            <display>The units for the standard deviation are the __________ units used to measure the observations.</display>
            <response>same</response>
            <display>The units for the standard deviation are the same units used to __________ the observations.</display>
            <response>measure</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>__________ refers to how individual observations vary and standard error refers to how multiple observations vary.</display>
            <response>standard deviation</response>
            <display>Standard deviation refers to how __________ observations vary and standard error refers to how multiple observations vary.</display>
            <response>individual</response>
            <display>Standard deviation refers to how individual observations vary and __________ refers to how multiple observations vary.</display>
            <response>standard error</response>
            <display>Standard deviation refers to how individual observations vary and standard error refers to how __________ observations vary.</display>
            <response>multiple</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>A __________ describes the likelihood that observations will occur within any range of values.</display>
            <response>distribution</response>
            <display>A distribution describes the __________ that observations will occur within any range of values.</display>
            <response>likelihood</response>
            <display>A distribution describes the likelihood that __________ will occur within any range of values.</display>
            <response>observations</response>
            <display>A distribution describes the likelihood that observations will occur within any __________ of values.</display>
            <response>range</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ of a distribution between a range of values represents the probability that a new observation will fall within that range also.</display>
            <response>density</response>
            <display>The density of a distribution between a __________ of values represents the probability that a new observation will fall within that __________ also.</display>
            <response>range</response>
            <display>The density of a distribution between a range of values represents the __________ that a new observation will fall within that range also.</display>
            <response>probability</response>
            <display>The density of a distribution between a range of values represents the probability that a new __________ will fall within that range also.</display>
            <response>observation</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>A __________ distribution is symmetric, so for example, the probability between -1 and 0 is equal to the probability between 0 and 1.</display>
            <response>normal</response>
            <display>A normal distribution is __________, so for example, the probability between -1 and 0 is equal to the probability between 0 and 1.</display>
            <response>symmetric</response>
            <display>A normal distribution is symmetric, so for example, the __________ between -1 and 0 is equal to the probability between 0 and 1.</display>
            <response>probability</response>
            <display>A normal distribution is symmetric, so for example, the probability between -1 and 0 is __________ to the probability between 0 and 1.</display>
            <response>equal</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ distribution has 68 percent of its observations in the range between -1 and 1 standard deviation.</display>
            <response>normal</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has __________ percent of its observations in the range between -1 and 1 standard deviation.</display>
            <response>68</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has 68 percent of its observations in the __________ between -1 and 1 standard deviation.</display>
            <response>range</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has 68 percent of its observations in the range between -__________ and __________ standard deviation.</display>
            <response>1</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ distribution has 95 percent of its observations in the range between -2 and 2 standard deviations.</display>
            <response>normal</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has __________ percent of its observations in the range between -2 and 2 standard deviations.</display>
            <response>95</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has 95 percent of its observations in the __________ between -2 and 2 standard deviations.</display>
            <response>range</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has 95 percent of its observations in the range between -__________ and __________ standard deviations.</display>
            <response>2</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <display>The __________ distribution has 99.7 percent of its observations in the range between -3 and 3 standard deviations.</display>
            <response>normal</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has __________ percent of its observations in the range between -3 and 3 standard deviations.</display>
            <response>99.7</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has 99.7 percent of its observations in the __________ between -3 and 3 standard deviations.</display>
            <response>range</response>
            <display>The normal distribution has 99.7 percent of its observations in the range between -__________ and __________ standard deviations.</display>
            <response>3</response>
        </cluster>



    </clusters>
</setspec>