<setspec>
    <clusters>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The heart is in the middle of the __________.</display>
            <response>chest</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>First the blood flows into __________ called arteries.</display>
            <response>tubes</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>First the blood flows into tubes called __________.</display>
            <response>arteries</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The __________ that leave the heart are thick tubes.</display>
            <response>arteries</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The arteries that leave the heart are __________.</display>
            <response>thick tubes</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The closer to the heart, the fewer the __________ there are, and the larger they are.</display>
            <response>veins</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>First moving away from the heart in the __________, then traveling to various parts of the body in capillaries, and lastly going back to the heart through the veins.</display>
            <response>arteries</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>First moving away from the heart in the arteries, then traveling to various parts of the __________ in capillaries, and lastly going back to the heart through the veins.</display>
            <response>body</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>First moving away from the heart in the arteries, then traveling to various parts of the body in __________, and lastly going back to the heart through the veins.</display>
            <response>capillaries</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>First moving away from the heart in the arteries, then traveling to various parts of the body in capillaries, and lastly going back to the heart through the __________.</display>
            <response>veins</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>__________ can flow from the atria down into the ventricles, because there are openings in the horizontal septum that separates them.</display>
            <response>Blood</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can flow from the __________ down into the ventricles, because there are openings in the horizontal septum that separates them.</display>
            <response>atria</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can flow from the atria down into the __________, because there are openings in the horizontal septum that separates them.</display>
            <response>ventricles</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can flow from the atria down into the ventricles, because there are __________ in the horizontal septum that separates them.</display>
            <response>openings</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can flow from the atria down into the ventricles, because there are openings in the horizontal __________ that separates them.</display>
            <response>septum</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The heart is a double __________ whose two parts work in unison.</display>
            <response>pump</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The heart is a double pump whose two parts work in __________.</display>
            <response>unison</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow back and forth between the left and right __________ of the heart, because the septum that separates them is solid, keeping the two circles separate.</display>
            <response>halves</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow back and forth between the left and right halves of the heart, because the __________ that separates them is solid, keeping the two circles separate.</display>
            <response>septum</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow back and forth between the left and right halves of the heart, because the septum that separates them is __________, keeping the two circles separate.</display>
            <response>solid</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow back and forth between the left and right halves of the heart, because the septum that separates them is solid, keeping the __________ separate.</display>
            <response>two circles</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The left __________ of the heart sends blood out through a big artery and from there, into branching arteries that carry it to various parts of the body.</display>
            <response>ventricle</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The left ventricle of the heart sends blood out through a big artery and from there, into branching __________ that carry it to various parts of the body.</display>
            <response>arteries</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The left ventricle of the heart sends blood out through a big artery and from there, into branching arteries that carry it to __________ of the body.</display>
            <response>various parts</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The __________ that carry blood back from the body parts empty the blood into the right atrium of the heart.</display>
            <response>veins</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The veins that carry blood back from the __________ empty the blood into the right atrium of the heart.</display>
            <response>body parts</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The veins that carry blood back from the body parts empty the blood into the __________ of the heart.</display>
            <response>right atrium</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The blood then flows down into the right ventricle, which pumps it into the __________ and back to the heart, into the left atrium.</display>
            <response>lungs</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>It brings __________ to the body cells and takes away their carbon dioxide.</display>
            <response>oxygen</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>It brings oxygen to the body cells and takes away their __________.</display>
            <response>carbon dioxide</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>As the blood flows through the capillaries in the body, carrying its supply of oxygen, it also collects __________.</display>
            <response>carbon dioxide</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The blood is then pumped into the __________, and then to the lungs.</display>
            <response>right ventricle</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The blood is then pumped into the right ventricle, and then to the __________.</display>
            <response>lungs</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood from the heart flows through these __________, passing carbon dioxide into the tiny air sacs.</display>
            <response>capillaries</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood from the heart flows through these capillaries, passing __________ into the tiny air sacs.</display>
            <response>carbon dioxide</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood from the heart flows through these capillaries, passing carbon dioxide into the __________.</display>
            <response>tiny air sacs</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The oxygen-rich blood is returned to the left atrium of the heart and pumped out to the body through the __________.</display>
            <response>left ventricle</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The __________ starts with the atria, which push blood into the ventricles.</display>
            <response>contraction</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The contraction starts with the __________, which push blood into the ventricles.</display>
            <response>atria</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The contraction starts with the atria, which push __________ into the ventricles.</display>
            <response>blood</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The contraction starts with the atria, which push blood into the __________.</display>
            <response>ventricles</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Then the __________ of the ventricles squeeze together and force the blood out into the arteries.</display>
            <response>walls</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Then the walls of the __________ squeeze together and force the blood out into the arteries.</display>
            <response>ventricles</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Then the walls of the ventricles squeeze together and force the blood out into the __________.</display>
            <response>arteries</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The __________ is the first part of the heartbeat.</display>
            <response>contraction</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The contraction is the __________ of the heartbeat.</display>
            <response>first part</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>The contraction is the first part of the __________.</display>
            <response>heartbeat</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>After that, the heart __________ relaxes, which is the second part of the heartbeat.</display>
            <response>muscle</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>After that, the heart muscle relaxes, which is the second part of the __________.</display>
            <response>heartbeat</response>
        </cluster>
        <cluster>
            <displayType>Cloze</displayType>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>__________ can not flow backward into the arteries because little trapdoors called valves stop it.</display>
            <response>Blood</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow backward into the __________ because little trapdoors called valves stop it.</display>
            <response>arteries</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow backward into the arteries because little __________ called valves stop it.</display>
            <response>trapdoors</response>
            <parameter>0</parameter>
            <display>Blood can not flow backward into the arteries because little trapdoors called __________ stop it.</display>
            <response>valves</response>
        </cluster>
    </clusters>
</setspec>
